[wind blowing]
- Before you do
what you're about to do,
there is something
you should know.
- What?
- There's something
I just found out--
all of us just found out.
- Oh, my God.
- I'm not sure
how all this ends.
So I just wanted
to give you a heads-up.
- Oh, my God.
[dramatic music]
[sighs]
I feel like I'm gonna pass out
right now.
♪ ♪
It's just, like, the last thing
that I needed to hear.
- This season
of "The Bachelor"
is an unbelievable journey
like you've never seen before.
- Peter!
[all cheering]
- Peter flies in, and he's
looking so freaking delicious,
like, I just wanna
lick him up and down.
- [squeals]
Peter is my dream man.
- He's just hot.
He's just sexy.
- To new beginnings!
[both cheering]
- We have
an undeniable connection.
Physically, there's a spark.
- Every single time
I'm with you,
it gets better and better.
- I am falling in love
with Peter,
and I can't get enough of him.
- Crazy in love.
That's the type of true love
that I'm after.
- Mm.
Today I realized
I was in love with Peter,
but if he sleeps
with anybody else,
it's gonna be hard for me
to continue to move forward.
- You gave him an ultimatum...
- [gasps]
- And I'm sorry.
It's disgusting.
- This drama, these lies--
he's being blindsided.
- Shut the [bleep] up.
- You shut the [bleep] up!
- [sobbing]
When you made that decision,
it was literally like a slap
in my face.
- [screams]
- Dude, she has waited
this long
to tell him she's a virgin?
- I don't want this
just to feel like
it's all about the sex,
but I have been intimate.
I can't lie to you about that.
- It just hurts.
It hurts really bad.
[all sobbing]
- I'm just so scared.
- Like, why am I even here?
- How do you just walk away
and just give up?
Like, I still feel it
and I want to fight,
but there is so much right now
that's just
destroying my heart.
- Get--like, I can't.
I'm so [bleep] done!
- Don't let her go.
Don't let her go.
Bring her home to us.
- When I love someone,
I don't care
how hard it looks.
I will never surrender,
'cause I do believe that
love conquers all.
- The dramatic
three-hour premiere
of "The Bachelor"
takes off right now.
[engines rumbling]
[birds chirping]
[inspiring music]
♪ ♪
- Prop clear!
[engine turns over]
I am so excited.
I have no idea what's coming,
but I know that my life
will never be the same.
♪ ♪
I'm taking a leap of faith
being the Bachelor
and opening up my heart again.
♪ ♪
But I have faith
this is gonna work,
and I'm gonna go find my wife.
♪ ♪
I've been in love before,
and it's the greatest feeling
in the world.
You have no idea how much
I'm falling for you right now.
I never expected to feel
the way I felt with Hannah.
♪ ♪
both: Whoo!
- I fell in love.
I felt it with my heart 100%.
I love Hannah Brown.
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
- Yes.
Could definitely
get used to waking up
next to you every morning.
♪ ♪
Unfortunately, I was left
with a broken heart.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[inhales shakily]
[sighs]
♪ ♪
- You know, when you came home,
my heart went out to you
because I knew that you were
madly, head-over-heels in love.
- I mean, you could just see it
in your face, but--
- Yeah.
Even though I was
in love with Hannah
and the relationship
didn't work out,
I'm taking so much
from that relationship
with me moving forward.
But, hey, everything happens
for a reason.
[both speaking Spanish]
- [laughs]
That's right.
- Everything happens
for a reason.
- Absolutely.
- It does, and now look at you.
You're the Bachelor.
- I know. That's just crazy.
- It is crazy.
- It's like, "What?"
I do still believe that
there is that next-level love,
that
once-in-a-lifetime-type love,
like what my parents have.
[both speaking Spanish]
- There's so much that I love
about my Cuban roots.
- I think you got
the flying gene from Daddy
and you got
the dancing gene from Mama.
- Mi Mamá Cubana.
The food's amazing.
The closeness, the dancing--
I have been so lucky
to just grow up in a family
with so much love.
It's big part of who I am,
and I'm so excited
to hopefully have a family
of my own one day.
- What are you looking for?
Like, what kind of girl?
Like, honestly.
- Yeah, I just--
I want that--that girl
that you, without a doubt,
can so confidently call
your best friend, you know?
Someone that just...
it sounds simple, but just has
a kind, sweet heart.
What I'm looking for is that
genuine, just true
connection with someone.
I'm so excited.
- Are you?
- My heart is beating
out of my chest,
and, uh,
I can't even believe it still.
Like, it's still
very surreal for me
that this is all
about to start.
- You have no idea
how life is about to change.
- You know, I'm in
the captain's chair now.
[intrepid music]
I'm going into this
truly trying to see
if I can find my person,
and I'm gonna give it my all.
- You the Bachelor?
- Yeah.
[laughs] How you doing?
- You are? Oh.
Can I take a picture with you?
- Of course, yeah.
[camera shutters snapping]
Just seeing all the love and
support, it's been so amazing.
Look at that.
- Choose me.
- Hey, I think
I found my copilot right here.
I don't need to go on the show.
- Oh, yes.
- I have such a good feeling
about this.
♪ ♪
This whole experience,
it works,
and I'm so excited
and so hopeful
that I'm gonna find love again.
♪ ♪
We're gonna have
one hell of an adventure.
♪ ♪
I'm gonna go find my wife.
[dramatic music]
- Coming up tonight...
- Welcome aboard flight 143
with direct service
to Peter's heart.
- Put your tray tables up...
- I'm going for
the mile-high club.
- Your seats
in the upright position.
- If a girl taxis an airplane
in here right now,
I'm gonna lose my mind.
- Because Peter's romantic
journey takes flight.
- Whoo!
- Oh!
- Honey, there are some cats
and some rats!
- [gasps]
- You kissed him?
- I'm so happy for you.
- Yeah.
- We could honestly
be the greatest love story
of all time.
- [screams]
- Oh, my God.
It's Hannah Brown.
- Hey.
- [gasps]
- And then...
[laughter]
- Oh, my God.
- It's the first date
of the season.
- I feel so hopeful.
- Let's go!
- When I have my eye
on something, like Peter,
I'm gonna go after it.
- It's all happening
tonight...
- Whoo-hoo!
- On the three-hour
"Bachelor" premiere.
[wistful music]
♪ ♪
- Tonight's the night.
I'm the Bachelor now.
That's insane.
I don't know what I did
to deserve this.
♪ ♪
I have all the faith
that I'm gonna find,
you know,
my wife from this.
I'm ready to open up my heart,
and I'm hoping that
all these women are ready
to do the exact same thing
with me.
I cannot wait
to start this whole journey
and to meet all these
amazing women.
I'm so excited.
[bright music]
[car horn honks]
♪ ♪
- Hi, I'm Alexa.
I'm 27.
I'm a caregiver.
I love caring for people,
I really do,
and it fulfills me.
All right, take some
deep breaths for me.
All right, one, two, three.
- [yelps]
- I also wax vaginas
for a living.
[laughs]
I own my own business,
and I love it.
People trust me
with their bodies,
and I don't take that lightly.
I wax every part of the body:
sideburns, lips,
chin, neck, boobs.
You got hairy knuckles?
I got you.
Waxing is a lot like love:
you have to bare it all,
and I'm ready
to bare it all to Peter,
and I hope he's ready
to bare it all to me.
- Hey, everyone,
my name's Hannah Ann,
and welcome
to Knoxville, Tennessee.
I started to model
when I was 16 years old.
I grew up
in such a small town.
Modeling really gave me
the opportunity to travel
and to be
around different people.
I got it!
But ultimately,
I'm just a normal girl.
[laughs]
- Heavenly Father,
thank you for this day.
- My relationship
with my family--
we are all very close.
- Well, I'm excited
and nervous at the same time.
Seems like a nice young man.
- My dad already talks
about Peter like he knows him.
The other night, he was like,
"I think Peter seems like
a very good guy."
And my sister goes, "Dad,
you don't even know Peter."
Pretty soon, he might be
sitting right there
right across from Dad.
Right in front of Daddy-O.
I cannot wait to meet Peter.
I could just meet him
the first night
and he could just be like,
"Oh, man,
"let's just forget
about all of this.
Let's just fly away."
To Peter.
all: Cheers.
[laughter]
[dramatic music]
- [grunting]
♪ ♪
- Hi, I'm Tammy.
Welcome to Syracuse.
I've always been a fighter
since I was a kid.
In high school,
I was on a boys' wrestling team
and the guys just go in
and they're like,
"Oh, no, she's gonna be
like a little girl."
And then I pin you
in the first round,
and then what?
[hammer tapping]
I'm a real estate agent.
I actually flip houses
as well.
I'm gonna go in--
smash down walls if I need to,
rearrange rooms if I need to,
and I'm not afraid of that.
So I'm very happy
with what I've achieved
at such a young age.
I travel a lot.
So I love Peter
because he's a pilot,
and I'm a jet-setter.
Like, if he's not my person,
I don't know who is.
Like, I'm sorry that he had
his heart broken by Hannah,
but you're mine.
I'm gonna grab you,
and you're mine.
[monitor beeping]
- I'm Victoria Paul.
I am 27 years old.
It's good
to see you guys again.
I'm a nurse.
Taking care of regular patients
is my favorite.
- Are you married yet?
- Not yet.
- Not yet?
- I think
the most fulfilling thing
about being a nurse is being
able to help someone
who can't help themselves.
Growing up, I was
my sister's primary caregiver
because my dad passed away
when I was two
and my mom
fell into addiction.
[pensive music]
There were times that
my sister and I didn't know
where our next meal
would come from
or didn't have clothes
or shoes that would fit.
So I'd say I had to grow up
pretty--pretty fast
pretty young.
- I know that you're gonna
find love on this journey.
- I'm ready
to have a son-in-law.
[laughs]
- I didn't think that there was
hope for my mom, and...
there was.
- I love you.
- She's found sobriety,
and I'm just really proud.
- So, are you excited?
Are you?
- Mm-hmm.
Peter just seems so genuine
and so true.
I could definitely see myself
falling for him.
So I'm really excited
about that,
and I'm kind of overwhelmed
with emotion because--
because I've wanted that
for so long.
[dynamic music]
♪ ♪
- Good morning.
- I'm Kelley.
I'm 27 years old.
I'm an attorney.
Hey, Dad?
- Yes, my dear?
- I work with my entire family.
- What's this dude's story?
Do you even know who he is?
- He's a pilot.
I try to separate
my dating life from my family
because my brothers are
super overprotective.
- We gotta ask him if he's
joined the mile high club.
all: Oh.
- Oh, my God.
- That's disgusting.
He could be married
to your sister.
[all laugh]
- I'm really excited
that Peter's the Bachelor
because I've met Peter.
[laughs]
I was in California
for one of my
best friends' weddings
and saw Peter
in the lobby.
[laughs]
I guess he was there
for his ten-year reunion.
It's hard
not to look at that situation
and think that wasn't
a major sign being sent to me
to be like, "Hey, you should
really do this."
And who knows?
Maybe at the end of it,
I'll be engaged.
[laughs]
- Okay, Madi,
you're gonna be right here.
The Bachelor's gonna be
right here.
In between you
and the Bachelor,
there's gonna be
all the other girls.
- Right.
- I want you
to do whatever it takes
to get from right here
to right here.
- I'm Madison Prewett,
and I'm from Auburn, Alabama.
I've won four
state championships
in basketball throughout
my high school career,
all coached by my father.
- All right, set him up
for the crossover.
Here we go, here we go.
- We have
a super close relationship.
I love you.
I would describe myself
as a challenger.
I'm someone
who likes a good challenge,
and I like to challenge others.
♪ ♪
[laughs]
[bells ringing]
I am so excited
that the Bachelor is Peter.
[laughs]
I just think he is really sweet
and really genuine,
and he's also someone
who seems like he can have fun
and go on, like,
fun adventures--
obviously, with his job.
And I love to travel,
so I would be
so down for that.
[laughs]
Dad, I know you've been there
for me
my whole life,
but don't worry.
I got this.
I'm ready.
[clicks tongue, laughs]
♪ ♪
- So what brings you in today?
- You know, I've just been
a little uncomfortable
with a couple of things
with my body, and I thought,
"Why not now?"
- My name is Maurissa.
I am 23 years old.
I am a patient care coordinator
for two plastic surgeons.
I absolutely love my job.
I get to make these women
feel great about themselves,
and that's important to me
because of everything
that I've gone through.
When I was younger,
I was crowned
Miss Montana Teen USA,
but there were things
in the blogs saying,
"Oh, Montana
has a beautiful face,
but her body is gonna
ruin it for her."
And that really
made me struggle.
I didn't want to eat
because of everything
that they were saying
about me.
So when I decided I didn't
want to do pageants anymore,
I just let go of myself,
and I ended up actually
gaining about 80 pounds.
And then, finally,
I just woke up one day like,
"It's time to get
your stuff together, Maurissa.
Let's go."
And I became
the confident, real person
that I am today.
- Cross, hook, cross, duck.
- Now that I've taken control
of my life,
I'm finally ready
to find that person
to share everything with.
I'm gonna knock
that competition out of here!
- Coming up...
- Are you ready for round five?
- Round five.
- The women arrive...
- Okay.
- ♪ I'm in love ♪
- On a night...
- [screams]
- Full of shocking surprises.
- Hey.
- Guys!
- Guys, we have a crisis.
- Hannah is here.
- Oh, my God.
- Is she competing?
Is that legal?
- [gasps]
- The beast is back, bitches.
- And later...
it's Peter's first date.
- I got a need.
I got a need for Peter.
Whoo!
- Let's go!
[women squealing]
Ladies.
- Some of the girls
are gonna be real upset.
- Last night brought out
the worst in people.
- It's like a ticking, ticking,
ticking time bomb.
- You're cheating.
That's cheating.
- They have a past,
and we all know that.
- This is what
I didn't want to do.
- It's all happening tonight
on this special three-hour
"Bachelor" premiere.
[sweeping music]
♪ ♪
- This is it.
I'm looking for love,
and these ladies are looking
for love as well.
This is hopefully
gonna go down
as the most
beautiful love story ever.
I know what I have to offer.
I know this heart and how much
love I have to give.
I just need to find someone
that wants to accept that
and is willing
to give the same to me,
and I can't wait
to meet her tonight.
I know this is gonna be
an amazing night,
and I just--I want it
to happen, like, right now.
Like, let's go.
[laughs]
- It's happening.
- You think this guy's ready?
- Pop the champagne!
[cork pops, women scream]
- That is insane!
- There goes
my spray tan, honey.
- Cheers to Peter.
[all cheering]
- Finding our copilot!
[all cheer, laugh]
♪ ♪
- Wow, wow, wow.
[exhales sharply]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Peter.
- Chris.
- Welcome home.
- Thank you, man.
[laughs]
- Welcome back to your mansion.
- Wow.
both: Good to see you.
- Man, you look sharp.
- Yeah.
- Tuxedo.
- Are you feeling it?
- You got a little Bond thing
going on.
- Yeah, I'm feeling it.
This is a big night.
- You seem a little fidgety.
You seem a little nervous.
- Yeah, little bit.
It's good nerves, though.
Good nerves.
I, uh--it's a big night,
and hopefully, you know,
tonight I meet, you know,
the girl of my dreams
and someone I can just
spend the rest of my life with.
You know, I had the most
amazing experience in my life
the last time around,
and it did work for me,
and it was
such a beautiful journey.
And, yes, I wish it, you know,
would have ended up
a little bit different,
but, you know,
now we have this.
- Are you over that?
Are you over that heartbreak?
Are you over Hannah?
- I am, I am.
Again, I would not
be here tonight
if I wasn't ready to put that
behind me and move forward.
I'm so hopeful
that at the end of this, uh,
you know, I can find that love.
- You ready
to meet these women?
- I can't wait, man.
I cannot wait.
- The first limo is pulling in
right now.
Peter...
- Oh, my God, man.
- Good luck, brother.
- Thanks, Chris.
- Let the journey begin.
- Thank you.
- Oh, my gosh,
he looks so cute!
- Are you excited?
- Can someone pinch me?
- Is this real life?
[all laugh]
all: Peter!
[all cheering, clapping]
- [laughs]
[exhales sharply]
♪ ♪
[romantic music]
Wow.
- [giggles]
- Hi, there.
- Hi, how are you?
- I'm great.
How you doing?
- Nervous.
- Yeah?
- Very nervous.
- I'm Peter.
- I'm Alayah.
- Alayah, so nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
So family is something
that's super important to me,
and so before coming,
my grandma wrote you a letter.
- No.
- She did!
I have this for you.
It's from my Grandma Rose.
- Stop.
Rose?
- Rose. Grandma Rose.
- My grandmother's name
is Rose.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- No.
- Rose Betha.
- Oh, Rosemary.
- No way.
- Yes.
I have no idea what it says.
So we can
figure it out together.
- We'll read it together then.
- Okay.
- Awesome.
- It was nice to meet you.
- Thank you so much.
Yeah, so nice to meet you.
I'll see you inside, okay?
- I'll see you inside.
- All right.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
Excellent way
to start the night.
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
[car door closes]
Hi.
- Wow, you look gorgeous.
- Thank you.
- How you doing?
- Good, how are you?
- I'm so good.
I'm Peter.
- So nice to meet you.
- Very nice to meet you.
- Yes, so I am Sydney.
- Sydney.
- Yes, and I am from Alabama.
- Okay.
[both laugh]
- Um, but I'm not
your typical southern girl,
and not every girl from 'bama
makes bad decisions.
[laughs]
- Throwing some shade.
I'll take it.
- I'm so excited to see you.
- I'm so happy
to have you here.
- I'm so excited to make
some time with you inside.
- Well, thank you
for being here.
- Thank you.
- I'll see you inside.
Beautiful dress.
- Thank you.
- Alabama city.
All right.
[laughs]
[car door closes]
[upbeat music]
Hello.
- Hi, how are you?
- I'm so good.
How you doing?
- Good.
- I'm Peter.
- I'm Hannah Ann.
- Hannah Ann.
I love that name.
- Well, hopefully
you can save room
for another Hannah
in your heart.
- Yes, I think I can.
- I am so thankful
that you're the Bachelor,
and I know
that we're gonna have
such a great time together.
- I can't wait.
- Yes, I'm excited.
- Yeah, this'll be great.
So nice to meet you.
- Can't wait to see you
later on.
- See you inside.
both: All right, bye.
- [sniffs]
Whoo.
Wow, I'm in trouble.
Oh, boy.
It's gonna be a fun night.
- ♪ I'm in love ♪
[laughs]
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Hi, Peter.
- How you doing?
[both laugh]
- I'm good.
- So nice to meet you.
- I'm Sarah.
- Sarah?
Well, welcome.
- Thanks.
I think my stomach might
actually leave my body
from all the butterflies
that I have.
- Oh, I 100% feel you.
- You look fantastic.
Like, hello.
Hubba-hubba.
- Gorgeous.
Absolutely gorgeous.
- Thank you.
- Just a little spin there.
Show off that beautiful dress.
- Oh, hello.
Already?
- I'm loving it.
- I can't wait
to talk to you more.
- Yeah.
I'll see you inside, okay?
- See you inside.
- All right.
[chuckles]
- Hi.
- Hello.
- How are you?
- I am so good.
How are you doing?
- Handsome. I'm well.
- It's very nice to meet you.
I'm Peter.
- Thank you.
I'm Lauren.
- Lauren.
Well, welcome.
- I would be lying
if I told you
that this whole thing
wasn't really scary for me...
- It is, yeah.
- But someone
really close to me once said,
"If it scares you, do it."
- I love that.
- And I'm really excited to
begin this journey with you.
- You ready for it?
- I'm ready for it.
- It's gonna be a lot of fun.
- Yes.
- Yeah, I can't wait.
- Nice to meet you.
- All right, it was very nice
to meet you.
Love the suit.
That's a power suit
right there.
- Thank you.
- Yes, rocking it.
- [laughs]
- Wow, she is gorgeous.
Oh, boy.
[car door opens]
[chuckles]
[exhales sharply]
- Hi, Peter.
- Hello, beautiful.
It's so nice to meet you.
- It's so nice to meet you.
- Welcome.
- My name is Victoria...
- Victoria.
- And something that my niece
and I do when we're nervous--
we happy dance
the scaries away.
- The happy dance?
- Ready.
Bust a happy dance move.
- ♪ Do the happy dance ♪
♪ Hey, hey, whoo, what ♪
Let's go!
[laughs]
This is gonna be a good night.
That was awesome.
- It's gonna be a great night.
- I'm feeling good.
- I can't wait to talk to you.
- All those nerves
are gone now.
Let's go.
Let's have a great night.
- Yes, perfect, mine too.
See you tonight.
- Okay. We'll see you.
- This feels so surreal
for me.
There's no way
this is really happening,
that he is a real person.
Like, he is so perfect.
- Peter looks so incredible.
- Yeah.
- He looks like a doll.
Seriously.
- He's literally a doll.
- Peter is so handsome.
I just can't
wrap my brain around it.
He's got his
cute little tuxedo on
and his bow tie.
I mean, he's just looking good.
- I need to check this out
for a second.
- You need to check this out?
- I just need to...
- Do you like what you see?
- See what's going on here.
- Can you work with this?
- Okay.
- Yeah?
- Before I even came here,
I had a huge crush on Peter,
and now I could potentially
become future Mrs. Weber.
Like, what?
- We're gonna
pinky promise each other...
- Okay.
- That throughout our journey
together...
- Yes.
- We are gonna remain true
to ourselves...
- True to ourselves.
- Stay honest with each other.
- Always honest.
- And always dance
like nobody is watching.
- Always dance and have
a good time, I love that.
- He's just like that guy
you dreamt of marrying
as a little girl.
Like, thank you, Hannah.
Like, thank you.
all: I know!
- I just wanna say
I think Hannah made a mistake
by letting you go,
and I'm really excited
to be here
and get to know you more.
- Hot babe, mansion.
It doesn't get any better
than this.
♪ ♪
- Hi, there.
- Hi!
So nice to finally meet you.
- So nice to meet you too.
I love your wings.
- You look dapper.
- You look amazing. Beautiful.
- Thank you, I appreciate that.
- Yeah, you're welcome.
- So, you know,
all the girls have planned
such big
and over-the-top entrances,
but I figured since
I'm a flight attendant and--
- You're--no way.
That's so funny.
- Yeah, and you're a pilot...
- I am.
- So I figured
I would just "wing" it.
- No, I love the wings.
I'm looking for my copilot.
So awesome.
I can't wait.
- Nice meeting you.
- So nice to meet you.
- He's gonna be
meeting so many girls.
Like, it's gonna be hard
to remember all the names.
But because
I'm a flight attendant,
I'm different, you know?
- So I'm a flight attendant.
- Ooh.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- So hopefully
he sees something in me
that he doesn't see
in other girls.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome aboard Flight 143
with direct service
to Peter's heart.
- [laughs]
- My name is Megan; I'll be
your purser this evening.
- Yes.
- Oh, my God,
another flight attendant.
- Are you
a flight attendant too?
- I--yes, I am
a flight attendant.
- She's a flight attendant!
- There are so many women--
- So apparently everyone
and their mother
is a flight attendant,
but I'm not worried.
I mean, I'm here
for the "flight" reasons.
- A paper airplane.
Okay.
- Big paper airplane!
Let's go!
[laughs]
- Yes.
You got some skills up there.
Okay.
- Okay.
- I'm feeling it.
- And she sticks the landing!
- Boom! Yes.
- Whoo!
- 10 out of 10.
I'll take it.
- [laughs]
Hi, how are you?
- How you doing? I'm so good.
- I'm Madison.
- Madison? Peter.
- Yeah, it's so nice
to meet you.
- Wow. That was
such a cool entrance.
- So I successfully landed
my plane...
- You did.
- So hopefully all that's
left to do is land your heart.
- Aww, that's so sweet.
- Yeah.
- Thank you so much.
- It is so nice to meet you.
- I feel like the luckiest guy
in the world right now.
I mean, this really is
the craziest flight of my life.
We got some, uh, TSA here.
- Yeah.
They told me
there was a large package
in front of the mansion.
- Is that what you heard?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna have to do some
private screening.
So I'll see you on the inside.
- You know, maybe we'll expect
some turbulence along the way.
- I'm sure you're probably
gonna have a lot
of nauseating conversations.
Just in case,
I wanna give this to you.
- Barf bag.
But I'm at the controls,
and I just gotta
find my copilot
and we'll be sailing off
into the sunset.
[laughs]
[dramatic music]
Shut up.
[laughs]
If a girl taxis an airplane
in here right now,
I'm gonna lose my mind.
[wheels squeaking]
[metal clattering]
[music winds down]
[laughs]
- Hi, Peter!
- What's up?
- [laughs]
I'm coming for ya!
Hopefully I don't hit
any turbulence on my way up!
- Hey, smooth skies ahead!
- I'm going for
the mile-high club, you know?
I'm in it to win it.
- That was
the best entrance ever.
- Was it a good entrance?
- I loved it.
- Did you love it?
- That's the way to my heart,
right there.
- Okay, good.
- Awesome, yeah.
- I feel like you have to
do something cool
to impress Peter.
I came out on an airplane.
You can't really beat that.
[laughs]
[wheels rumbling]
- What is this?
Got some baggage?
[quirky music]
Thank you, sir.
[laughs]
There's no way
someone's in there.
- Oh, no.
If she's in the suitcase...
- [laughs]
Is she gonna jump out?
[laughs]
- Hello?
- No way.
[laughs]
- Peter?
[grunts]
- Hello?
No way.
- Peter!
- What?
- I would be scared
I'm gonna suffocate
if I was in a suitcase.
[quirky music]
- [laughing]
- Oh, my God, I am impressed.
Wow.
- Hi.
- Welcome.
What an entrance.
Here, let me, uh...
- Thank you.
- Help you off there.
- So...
- All right.
- Wow...
- Welcome.
- I've made it
to my final destination.
- It's like, are you a copilot
or are you baggage?
[all laugh]
- I love how calm he is.
Like, he has a calming thing
about him.
- He seems so genuinely...
both: Sweet.
- Like, he genuinely
wants to find somebody
to, like, do with life with,
and that, like, makes it
so much better.
- It does.
all: Hi!
- I mean, that's like some
David Copperfield [bleep].
We--we should
cut her in half later.
- We should.
- Where is he, right?
- I'm ready to meet my man.
[all laughing]
- Bring me Peter.
- This is gonna be
the ride of our lives.
[engine revving]
- Oh, yeah.
[radical rock music]
Whoo, baby!
♪ ♪
Okay.
- [laughs]
- Damn, that's sexy.
[laughs]
- Hello.
- I like the ride.
- Thanks.
Me, too.
- Wow.
You look absolutely gorgeous.
- Thank you.
I'm Lexi.
- I'm Peter.
- Nice to meet you.
- So nice to meet you.
- Clearly, I like to go fast.
I heard you do too.
- I do, yes.
- So you'll have
to catch me inside.
- You have the need for speed.
- Yes.
- It's like a old car.
- What a bad B.
- I think Lexi had
a pretty grand entrance,
but my paper airplane
is pretty close competition
with her red Corvette.
So we'll see which one
Peter likes better.
- Hello, there.
- Hi!
Well, hello, there.
- What do you have
on your back?
- I don't know, you tell me.
- I mean,
that looks like a windmill.
- I mean, I have one question
for you.
- What's that?
- Are you ready
for round five?
- Round five.
- We're stepping it up.
- Him and Hannah had some fun
in a windmill,
like, four times.
So I thought that I would
take it to the next level.
- Four times?
- [laughs]
- Four times!
Nice to meet you.
- It's very nice to meet you.
- Not once...
- Four times.
- Not twice...
- Not three...
all: But four.
- [speaking foreign language]
- [laughs]
- Four times?
[all laugh]
Four times?
Four times.
Like, let's make it ten.
- I think...
- Oh, my God.
Did you find that
in my car console?
- We might be able
to break the record!
- I mean,
you have to do something
to stand out in some way.
- You're gonna fall in love
with my hairless...
pussy...
- [laughs]
- Cat.
- Your pussycat.
- Yes!
- Oh, my God.
- Her name's Jasmine.
- 30 girls are meeting him.
So you gotta, like,
spice it up in some way.
- I'm so nervous.
- Don't be nervous.
- I'm, like, literally shaking.
- Hey, it's okay.
Nerves are good.
- Okay, so there's one thing
I want you to know about me...
- What's that?
- And it's that I have
a very dry sense of humor.
- Okay.
- But...
[laughs]
- But what?
- But that's
about the only thing...
- I knew that was going--
- That is dry about me.
- Oh, your jokes are great.
- Oh, thank God.
I feel like
I don't have to, like, go.
- That was like
the ultimate icebreaker.
- Should I call a taxi?
I should get in the limo.
- I want you to stay.
I'm gonna find you inside,
and that was amazing.
[both laugh]
[quirky music]
- There's so many girls here.
So you want to stand out.
It's important for me
to kind of establish myself
in the very beginning.
- What's your name?
- Victoria.
both: Victoria.
- Another Victoria.
- Oh, there's more Victorias?
- That's Victoria.
- That's the other Victoria.
- Oh, that's the other one?
- What's your last name?
Or what's the letter?
- Letter?
- F.
- I don't know her letter.
- Okay.
I don't want to be Victoria F.
I don't want to be
Victoria F.
That's bull.
[cow mooing]
- [laughs]
Hi, there.
- Hi.
- How you doing?
- I'm Jenna.
- Jenna. Peter.
- Nice to meet you.
- So nice to meet you.
Who's your friend?
- This is Ashley P.
- Okay.
- She's my emotional
support cow.
- "Emotional support cow"?
- Yeah.
So I figured you'd be
a little nervous tonight...
- Yeah.
- So you can hang on to her.
- Why, thank you.
- And I'm gonna go inside.
- Yeah, it was so nice
meeting you.
Welcome, and I'll talk to you
more inside, okay?
- See you soon.
- All right.
Got my emotional
support animal.
What's up, Ashley P.?
How you doing?
What do you think of her?
She a good catch?
Okay.
[Ashley P. moos]
All right.
both: Hi.
- How are you?
[testy music]
- That was a pony.
It's a pony.
- What?
What?
[laughs]
Ride 'em, cowboy.
- Mm, okay.
- You guys, there is a--
- There's a pony up there.
- A different species is there.
- It's a cow.
It's a cow.
- It's a cow?
- I was like, "Yeah, so this is
my emotional support cow.
"I know you're
a little nervous tonight.
If you need the cow,
here you go."
- Oh, okay, so it was
an emotional support.
- No, it was a joke.
It was like a joke.
- Good for you.
- Yeah.
- Go big or go home, right?
- Whatever.
- So I brought this...
- Ooh.
- And I want to blindfold you.
- Little blindfold action.
- Yes.
- Get down with that.
[sensual music]
- So I just want you to focus
on the way things feel...
- Okay.
- Because for me,
the way things feel
is most important...
- Okay.
- And right now,
everything feels just right.
♪ ♪
- That feels very right.
- [laughing]
- I love a bold woman.
- I'm trying to be bold.
I wanted to come in here
as bold as I possibly could
for him to remember.
So if he's
looking for somebody
to come out guns blazing--
pew-pew.
[laughs]
♪ ♪
- [laughing]
Hello.
- You look familiar.
- You do too.
- Kelley.
- How are you?
- I'm so good.
How you doing?
- Good.
Good to see you.
- It's so good to see you.
I was wondering
if you'd stop by.
- I met Peter a month ago
randomly in a hotel lobby.
I was here in California
for one of my
best friends' weddings,
and he was there
for his ten-year reunion.
So I'm gonna be honest
with you.
- Okay.
- I didn't really
want to do this.
- You didn't want to do this?
- No.
- Okay.
- At first.
And I kept saying
there would be a sign from God
that would tell me
if I should do this.
- Shut up.
How crazy was that?
- And I swear--
- In the hotel lobby.
- Correct.
- That's insane.
- Meeting you there,
I was like,
"I think this is
a pretty obvious sign."
- It was meant to be.
- I know.
- This is awesome.
Well, do you want to pick up
where we left off?
Remember that little dance
we were doing?
- Let's do it.
- You go one...
- [laughing]
- Two--there we go.
And then the dip.
Perfect.
You remember.
- I remember.
- I'm so happy you're here.
- I'm so happy I'm here.
- Oh, awesome.
- Let's see what happens.
I'll see you inside.
- Let's see.
Sounds good.
- Bye.
It was good
that he remembered me,
and I think the spark
is still there,
so that's just,
like, reassuring
that I want to be here.
- I was hoping she'd come by.
[laughs]
- I didn't know
if I want to do the show,
and I was like,
"There'll just be a sign, like,
if I should do this."
- Okay.
- And then a month ago,
I randomly ran into him
in a hotel.
- [gasps]
- I went and, like,
introduced myself.
- So did he remember you?
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
- Talk about a sign.
- Obviously,
Kelley has a one-up
because she has met Peter
in real life.
It's gonna benefit her
in this, I think.
- You could have gotten
any sign, and you got Peter.
So I'm like...
- [laughing]
- It's definitely feeling
more real now,
and looking around the room,
I see
a lot of very beautiful women.
So I'm just
sitting here praying
that nobody else walks through
those doors of this mansion.
- How you doing?
- I'm okay.
- I'm Peter.
- Hi, Alexa.
Nice to meet you.
- So nice to meet you.
- It's getting
a little too crowded.
Peter needs to come, like,
right now.
- My name is Avonlea.
- Avonlea.
- Yep, sounds just like
"heavenly."
- It does. Very heavenly.
- Yep.
[laughs]
- Peter, let's go!
We're open and ready for you!
- Hey, ladies.
How's it going?
- Oh, there she is!
- This is like sorority rush.
- Hi, Peter.
- Hello.
- I'm Natasha.
- It is so nice to meet you.
- Do you guys know
if there's, like, one more limo
or if, like, this is it?
- I don't know.
- No more girls.
We're good where we're at.
all: Cheers.
[dramatic music]
- Shut the front door.
- It's a damn
'nother limo, ladies.
- What?
Wait, he's still
meeting people?
This is, like, crazy.
- There's too many.
- Is there 40 of us now?
- Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
- What is going on?
- What's happening?
What is literally happening?
- Oh, my gosh.
- [gasps]
♪ ♪
- What?
[women screaming]
- Hey.
- [screams]
[women screaming]
- Hey.
- What?
- Is she--she dating him?
- Hannah.
- [laughs]
Hey.
You look good.
- Hello.
- Hey, bud, how are you?
- What are you doing here?
- Guys, we have a crisis!
Hannah is here!
- Hannah Brown is here
talking to Peter.
- Oh, my God--
- Is she competing?
- I don't know!
- Is that legal?
[laughs]
You've got to be
[bleep] kidding me.
- Well, you look very handsome.
- Yeah, you look gorgeous.
- How are you?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- Um--
- Was not expecting this.
- Uh, yeah, I'm sorry.
[both stammer]
- This is so weird right now.
- It is so weird.
- Do you remember, like,
a couple months ago?
- I do.
- Being, like, over here?
It's weird.
- How's it been?
- It's good.
- Good, good.
- It's exciting.
- Oh, I'm nervous.
- I feel like everyone's mood
just kind of, like, shifted.
- I know.
- Is she asking
for another shot at love?
Like, I mean, they obviously
have that chemistry
with each other.
So it's almost like
a slap in the face to us.
Like, why are we here, then?
Peter's everything
that I've dreamt of,
and to think that I might not
get that opportunity
because she's here,
it's frustrating.
- Where do you guys stand
if he lets her in?
- I don't know.
- If Hannah Brown
walks into this house,
I mean, it would be madness.
- When I heard that you were
gonna be the Bachelor...
- Mm-hmm.
- I had mixed emotions.
But when I stood where you are,
you wanted to
find your copilot,
and you gave me something.
- Aww.
- And I want you
to find that person,
and so I brought these back
for you.
- Hmm.
I was wondering
where these were,
but thank you for that.
- I still have 'em...
- I know.
- But...
- Um, no, that means a lot.
Seriously, thank you,
and, uh...
[sniffs, sighs]
Yeah.
- You're gonna be great.
[sweet music]
- [sighs]
Come here.
Thank you.
- I am really happy for you.
- What's going on?
- I'm just nervous.
I want him to come inside.
- He's been with her
for a long time, though.
- [sighs]
- I definitely want to know
what's up--like, now.
- Like, come on in, Peter.
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
- Hello, ladies.
[all cheering]
- Hi, this is for you.
- Hello.
Why, thank you.
Welcome aboard.
all: Yeah!
- I know some of you
may have seen, uh, Hannah.
She--she stopped by, and, um...
[pensive music]
Um, I fell in love with her--
I truly did--
and, um, you know,
she gave me back my wings.
Um, that's what I had given her
the first night.
And, uh--
no, it was really cool,
and I appreciated it.
Um, if anything,
this is just--
kind of seeing her tonight
is just giving me
even more hope, uh,
you know, moving forward
with all you beautiful ladies
that this can happen again,
and, you know, I can find love.
And thank you
for being courageous
to take this chance with me
and see if we can't find
some magic at the end of this.
[all laugh]
You all
look incredibly stunning.
Um, I am one lucky guy,
and I'm so happy to be here.
We'll see what happens.
So, um--
all: Yes.
- That being said,
I want to, uh, raise my glass
to all you beautiful women.
- Yes!
- May this be the beginning
of the greatest love story
we've ever seen.
- Yeah!
- Cheers to all of you.
[all cheering]
[indistinct chatter, laughter]
Let's get the party
started, yeah?
- Yeah!
- All right.
All right, let's go.
- It was really sweet
hearing what he had to say.
Hannah Brown--it's in the past.
They've officially closed
that chapter
with her returning the wings,
and he's ready to start
his new chapter here.
How are you feeling?
- I'm good.
I am excited.
This is, uh, pretty special.
- I've been nervous.
- Yeah?
Wait, I have
a special something.
- Yes!
- We gotta go
look at this letter.
- I know,
I'm kind of nervous.
My grandma's kind of
a little firecracker.
- Ooh.
All right, "Dear Bachelor"...
- [laughs]
- All right.
"Let me introduce you
to my granddaughter.
"She's looking for a soul mate.
A forever partner.
She's a romantic."
- I am a huge romantic.
- As am I.
"A lover of good looks"--
- Books.
- Oh, books.
- I mean, that too.
I love good looks.
That's fine.
Good books, especially.
- "Lover of good books."
That was bad.
"So you'll have to be
on your best behavior"...
- [laughs]
- "If you want to impress her.
"Be real, because she is.
Best of luck, Grandma Rose."
- [giggles]
That's my grandma!
- That means so much.
I love this.
- I, like, am blushing
so much right now.
- No, that is adorable to me.
- My grandma and I
are super close.
- That's awesome.
- Like, so close, and so--
- I can't tell you
how much that means.
- I feel like
actually getting to sit down
and talk with Peter really--
I don't know,
it just made it more real.
Like, holding his hand
and looking into his eyes.
He's just so sweet
and just so genuine.
- Peter looks like a dime.
Like, a dime-fifty.
- Yeah.
All things life, like, you need
to risk it for the biscuit,
and he looks like a really
[bleep] hot...
both: Biscuit.
- [laughs]
Buttery-flaky.
- I know.
I just wanna lick it all--
[laughs]
- You know, I've always been
that romantic--
that hopeless romantic.
- Same.
- You know?
- I know, I've been single
for, like, four years.
So--
- Four years?
No way.
- Yeah.
- Well...
- I'm hoping to find it.
- You're in the right spot now.
- I know, I'm excited.
- This is very exciting.
You have no idea.
- You're so handsome.
- You're beautiful too.
- Oh, thank you.
- I'm very, very excited
for this.
- Me, too.
This is gonna work.
- All right.
- This is so gonna work.
We gotta come up with a--
- We gotta make a handshake.
So boom to the five
to the pinky.
Kiss it.
Awesome.
- I definitely think
Peter can find what he had
with Hannah with me--
even better.
Like, sparks,
fireworks, everything--
and I won't break his heart.
[laughs]
- Cleared for take-off.
Whoo!
- Oh!
- Uh-oh.
- That was so bad.
- So...
- Yeah, yours did
get really far.
I'm actually really impressed.
- I kind of
impressed myself there too.
- Um, okay, so tell me
something interesting.
- When you really kind of
get to know me, I...
naturally am kind of
just a shy person.
- But I feel like
you're really real,
and, like,
you're so vulnerable,
and, like, I love that.
Like, I feel like that sets you
apart from so many people,
and, like, that was one thing
that just initially, like,
attracted me to you.
Um, but, yeah, I'm, like,
so excited that it was you.
- Aww, come here.
- I literally had
all my fingers crossed.
- I--I'm so happy you're here.
- I'm just excited.
Like, this is why I'm here.
Like, it makes everything
worth it, you know?
Like, all of the heartbreaks
and losses of the past--
I'm like, there's hope,
you know?
Like, there's someone
really great out there,
and hopefully it's him.
- [screams]
- It is him.
- Oh, my God!
[all screaming]
- Ladies.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Obviously,
our man's not here,
but that's a little something
for him.
- Yeah. Thanks!
- See you in a bit.
- Whoa. Wow.
- It's here.
- Oh, my God.
It's here, ladies.
- Wait, what
did he just bring in?
- The First Impression Rose.
So isn't that like
you're safe?
- Yes.
- It makes it real.
- Yeah.
- Chris Harrison comes by
and drops off
the First Impression Rose,
and then, like,
my heart starts beating.
Oh, my gosh.
Like, it's so daunting.
Like dun-dun, dun-dun.
- We're all going for it,
we all deserve it,
but only one of us
is gonna get it.
- People are definitely gonna
be more competitive now.
- Go find him.
- Okay.
- Get your time.
- It's on.
It's on like Donkey Kong.
[dramatic music]
- So I have a surprise
for you.
- I love surprises.
- So this is our putt-putt.
- No way.
Oh, my God.
- So you are gonna teach me...
- I think I can do that.
- How to play.
Can you?
- This looks like a famous--
- Is this familiar for you?
I figured it might be familiar.
- That I quite admire.
both: Yeah.
- I figured.
- Look at that.
It even spins and all.
- I know.
- All right.
This has been
such an amazing night so far.
Three.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Oh.
Well, you know what?
- Okay, you got me.
Wait--wait for it.
Look at that.
There we go.
I am on top of the world
right now.
[both laugh]
Whoo!
Yeah!
Let's go!
All the women I've met
tonight, they're just--
they're so sweet
and just adorable
and just fun.
- ♪ Uh-uh-uh-uh ♪
- Okay.
[laughs]
- ♪ Hey ♪
- I like it.
Boom-boom-boom.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey!
- Whoo!
- Oh!
- I'm already feeling, like,
an initial spark
with a lot of these women,
and I have
so much hope for this.
- My parents have been married
for over 26 years...
- No way.
- And they've always, like,
instilled in me, like,
one of the greatest gifts
you can give your children
is showing them
what a healthy marriage is.
And, like, I--
and I've been given that,
and I'm--I'm very blessed.
- I can't tell you how much
that means just hearing that,
'cause for me--for me,
family is everything.
And it's funny--my family is
probably ten minutes that way.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Super, super close.
- What are they laughing about?
- She might be funny.
It's cool.
- [laughs]
- But, like, how much time
is too much time?
- Once you interject--
- Go, go, go, go, go.
- I can't be that girl.
- Please.
- If I'm that girl,
people are gonna be like,
"Of course it's that girl."
- Can someone be that girl?
- Since I'm from
east Tennessee...
- Okay.
- Me and my dad
painted you a picture
of the Smoky Mountains.
- Hannah Ann, Oh, my God.
I love this.
This is so--
- And I was really nervous
to give it to you...
- Why?
- Because it's, like,
very personal.
- Hannah Ann, oh, my God.
This is--what an awesome gift.
Thank you so much.
- Yes.
- I absolutely love this.
I've got a good feeling
about this.
- I know, I do, I do.
- This is very exciting.
[tender music]
♪ ♪
[both gasp]
- Wait.
- They are making out.
♪ ♪
- This is so awkward.
- That's so uncomfortable.
- This is really awkward.
Let's not watch.
- I'm just gonna
mind my own business.
- I was almost, like,
with my blinders.
Like, I really don't
want to see this.
Like...
[exclaims]
- My lucky charm.
- My lucky charm!
- Off to a good start.
- Peter just gives me, like,
the butterflies,
and he makes me so excited.
Oh, man, I can't wait
to talk to him more.
- I want to talk to him now.
- I'm going next, bitch.
[laughs]
I'm just kidding.
I'm kidding,
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
But, no, I'm really
not kidding, actually.
- From what I can tell, Peter,
he likes a really bold girl.
I'm gonna have to cuff you.
- [laughs]
- Okay.
Oh.
Oh, okay.
- [laughs]
- Yep, mm-hmm.
So I had to
do another security check.
What you got in your pockets?
- What are we
working with here?
- [gasps]
Peter!
- Oh, my God,
are you kidding me?
You planted that.
- No, I didn't!
That was so in your pocket.
- Just stop it.
We're not doing that again.
- [laughs]
- That was good.
That was cute.
- [laughs]
[saucy music]
- Oh, more kisses.
- Shut the [bleep] up.
- Mm-hmm.
- I think
you need to uncuff me.
I didn't really think
I'd be feeling it that quickly
with so many of them.
I didn't expect to be
kissing so many girls either,
but it just kind of happened.
Um, yeah.
♪ ♪
- [giggles]
- They were kissing too?
[all chattering indistinctly]
- Peter has made out
with a few of the girls.
Again, I don't know
if that's him
or if it it's them.
- He's so cute.
How can you not kiss him?
- I think
that there's something
about being a reserved lady
that is also very beautiful
and mysterious.
- You had
such a mysteriousness about you
coming out of that limo.
I was very intrigued.
- I'm actually an open book...
- Okay.
- But it takes time.
- Yeah?
- Right?
- No, I mean,
I'm pretty much the same way.
And--
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh.
- Whoa, what is this?
We got some paper airplanes.
- Oh.
both: Oh.
- Sorry, girl.
Can I steal him for a second?
- Are you asking me?
'Cause the answer's no.
- Can you give us one minute?
- Yeah, yeah.
For sure, for sure.
- I'll bring the airplane.
All right.
- I know how I feel for Peter.
I know my feelings for him.
- This book
that I'm reading right now,
they talk about that.
How, like, doctors and pilots--
- That is my man.
I'm gonna get him.
- Duh-duh-duh-duh-duh.
- Okay.
- And you have to
still be like--
okay.
- We got the airplanes
coming in still, so--
- Sorry, girl.
- It is night one,
and, honey, there are some cats
and some rats!
[laughs]
- You can
make a good paper airplane.
- Airplane girl.
I like to consider myself
as a cat.
- One of my favorite
love stories ever
is my grandparents.
So my grandparents were married
for 61 years.
- 61 years?
- Yeah.
- I love that so much.
- And, like, I--holy shoot.
- Ooh.
- That is a big--
- Oh, what is that?
- Payback is a bitch.
- Love it.
Well, you know what?
- I'm gonna take him back.
- You took your two seconds.
I'm gonna take my two seconds.
- Actually, this is a gift
for both of you.
- Aww, you're so kind.
- Thank you.
- Kidding--just for you.
Fly away on it.
- I gave your two seconds
and I'll see you later, okay?
- Fly away on it.
- All right.
- Well, I know she's gonna
steal you in a second.
- Bye. Kisses.
- Yeah, no, it's okay.
I don't want this to end
right now.
- I really enjoyed this time
with you, Peter.
- I am so happy
that you're here right now.
I just have such a good feeling
about you...
- Totally.
- And I am feeling this
right now.
♪ ♪
- Tick-tock.
- This is awkward.
- Get used to it.
[both laugh]
- Okay, talk to you soon.
- All right.
- She one-upped me,
but you know what?
I kissed him.
So who's the real winner here?
- More kisses.
- You kissed him?
- Did you guys see other kisses
happening?
- [snarls]
- What?
- Honey, he is
on a kissing fever.
- I'm fine.
- [laughs]
- I'm so happy for you.
[testy music]
- It's hard to see
other people, like, kissing
and literally haven't even
gotten the chance
to even talk to him yet.
I really want
the First Impression Rose,
and I am freaking out.
- Who hasn't gotten time?
- I still have not
gotten my time.
- All right,
catch you guys later.
both: Bye.
- I'm anxious to be able
to talk to him again.
I'm not here to sit on a couch
and drink wine.
Like, I'm here to really
pursue, hopefully,
my future husband.
- Could I steal you
for a moment?
- Completely your choice.
Yeah, go ahead.
- For sure.
Is that okay?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- [gasps]
- No.
- Hannah cut me off.
Like, she's already talked
to Peter.
I was like, "Hey, like,
why would you double-touch
when you've already touched?"
- I'm not usually
the aggressive type,
but I wanted to
show the effort...
- You are, and it's very--
- And my boldness, and--
- It's noticed.
Thank you.
- I don't like this.
- Hannah Ann
got two times,
and I haven't even had one.
Like, I literally
don't understand.
- Well, thank you
for coming back.
- Yes, thank you.
- I feel like if I don't
have time with him now, like,
I'm gonna go home.
- So where are you from?
- I am from Las Vegas.
- Vegas, baby.
All right.
- Yeah, not your typical
Vegas girl.
Like, you know what I mean?
- Just that quality time?
- I'm more about, like,
being with my family,
hanging out
with my best friends.
- Could I steal you
for a minute?
- Hello.
Yeah, okay.
- It was so good
to finally talk to you.
- Yeah, thank you
for coming to find me.
I'll see you later, okay?
All right.
- So there was just one thing
Hannah Ann wanted to do
before this night ended.
- What's that?
- I felt like we needed
to end it with a kiss.
- With gifts?
- No, with a kiss.
- Oh, with a kiss.
[romantic music]
♪ ♪
- I don't understand.
- Well, that's a pretty
good gift too.
[chuckles]
♪ ♪
- Hannah Ann--
again, for the third time...
- What happened?
- Interrupted me.
- Hannah?
- Yeah, I had two minutes.
- No [bleep] way.
- My first time, and she--
- This is her third time.
- It really irked me to find
out that was her third time...
- Hey, Hannah,
can I talk to you for a second?
- Yeah.
- And I'm pissed about it.
You had your time twice.
That's fine, but, like, I want
to be able to speak my mind
and have my time with him
as well.
- Yeah, and--and I want that
for you too.
- [laughs]
Okay.
I, like, don't know if I, like,
should believe you or not.
Like, I don't know
what's going on.
- Hmm.
[tense music]
No, I mean--
- Like, I don't know
if you're being honest
or, like, [bleep] me
to get me out of your face.
Like, not that
I'm in your face,
but you know what I mean.
- No, no--
- Like, shoo me away.
- I don't think
you're in my face at all.
I think you've been very polite
and considerate
and honest and transparent,
and I really appreciate
and respect that.
So go out there and...
make a run for it, girl.
- [quietly] Seriously?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Well, I hope you have a good
rest of your night, girl.
- Yeah, of course, of course.
- Yeah.
- I'll catch you later on.
- Okay.
I'm gonna go this way.
♪ ♪
- Shiann pulling me aside--
I don't know.
I know that she feels behind,
but I'm trying
not to get caught up
with, like, the drama.
You know, I was brave
and I was courageous
and did something
out of my element
and went after what I wanted,
which I haven't
ever done before.
But when I have my eye
on something, like Peter,
I'm gonna go after it,
and I did.
- [weeping]
- The First Impression Rose.
Who do you think
is gonna get it?
- I don't know
who's gonna get it.
Hopefully me, but, um--
I mean, I guess we'll have to
see and wait and--
who that lucky girl is.
- Great.
- We're all freaking out about
the First Impression Rose.
Just wanna steal him
for a few minutes.
I have been waiting, like,
a long time.
I'm literally having
a [bleep] panic attack.
The fact
that this night could end
without getting
any time with him--
that's what's stressful.
- You said that your parents
have been married
for 30 years...
- Yeah.
- And so have mine.
- Oh, yeah? Okay.
- So that's, like, the love
that I'm looking for.
- Well, that's what
I'm looking for.
- Yeah.
- That's why we're here.
- That's what we're here for.
both: Yeah.
- Your eyes are insane.
- Thank you.
- Peter!
- Oh, my God.
[feedback squealing]
- Thank you.
- Peter!
- What's that?
- We need to talk.
- [laughs]
- Uh-oh, am I being summoned?
- Oh, no.
- Whenever you're done, like,
just meet me by the fire.
- Okay, I'll meet you
right there, all right?
- Okay.
- I'm so sorry.
[laughs] Can I steal you?
- Yeah, of course.
- Some girl in a bodysuit
intercepted my boo.
[feedback squeals]
- This is my gift to you...
- Aww.
- 'Cause I think I'm pretty
sweet, and I love sweets.
- What's your favorite color?
- I love strawberry,
so the red one.
- I've literally waited
all night,
and we're not
doing this anymore.
I'm frustrated.
Everyone's, like,
gotten more time with him.
I just, like--I haven't,
and the clock is ticking.
It's getting down to the wire.
Hi, Peter.
- Hello.
- Can I steal you for a second?
- Sure.
- I'm gonna try my hardest
to, like, be myself.
My heart is racing right now.
- How you feeling now?
- I'm good.
I was a little nervous, like,
um, coming into it.
Um, my, like...
little one-liner to you...
the dry thing...
- The--oh, that's right.
Yes.
No, that was good.
I--
- Was it?
- Yes, that was good.
- 'Cause I was, like,
super nervous about saying it,
but then I was like,
"Oh, my God."
Like...
- Wait, repeat--
what did you say, again?
I'm so sorry.
[stammering]
- No, you're good.
You have like 100 girls here.
It's fine.
Um, I was like,
"So the one thing
"I want you to know about me
is I have
a very dry sense of humor"--
- That's right.
That's the only thing
that's dry about you.
I was like, "Hey!"
And I finished it--
- Hey-oh.
- That's right.
I do remember that. Yes.
- You do.
And then I was like,
"Okay, wait,
"you can finish it for me.
That's so cute."
'Cause then you hugged me,
and then you spun me around
and I was like,
"Hey, that's cute."
- That's right.
Yeah, forgive me. I'm sorry.
- No, it's fine.
- Hey, guys.
- Hello.
- I totally hate to be
this person
and to interrupt you guys...
- No, you're good.
- But I'm gonna try to
steal you for a second, Peter.
- Let's do it, yeah.
- Yep, go for it.
- All right, it was great
talking to you.
- It was good talking to you.
- I'll see you later, okay?
- You look stunning,
by the way.
I love this dress.
- Thank you.
- You look stunning.
- You look gorgeous.
- You're so sweet.
How you doing?
- [sighs] I just had so many,
like, high expectations.
Like...
[sighs]
He didn't even remember
what I said.
It just sucks.
[sniffling]
- Hey, what's going on?
- I'm fine.
- What happened?
Can I get you, like, a towel?
- No...
- Or, like a...
- I'm okay.
Well, like,
what's-her-face came in
and, like, stole him
for, like, two minutes.
- Hey.
- [sniffling]
- Tell me how you're doing.
- I'm doing really good.
You know, I'm really excited,
really hopeful.
I had quite the experience
the last time,
and I'm so happy I have women
like you here with me.
How you doing, though?
- I'm good.
This kind of scary,
and walking up to--
to another female
and just being like,
"Hey, can I steal this person
from you?"
Like, it's so uncomfortable.
- By the way, you
are the sweetest stealer.
- I just feel like I just
didn't even get to say anything
and I was just, like, stupid.
And, like, he probably
doesn't even...
[sobbing]
To think, like,
that's the only conversation
that I get with him,
and, like, now he has to
base a decision
if I could be, like, his wife
or not off of that?
- If I get a rose tonight,
like, this is the first time
I have ever gotten a rose
from a guy.
Like--
- Really?
You've never
gotten flowers before?
- I've never
gotten flowers before.
- Aww.
- And so I am ready
to get my feet wet
and to get to know you
and to get to know your heart.
- Thank you for that,
and thank you for being bold.
- [weeping]
I'm just scared
that, like,
I'm gonna fall behind.
There are so many women
and they're so pretty
and, like...
[sighs]
They're so pretty.
- Good to see you.
Give me a hug.
- I am so happy that you came.
- I am happy I'm here.
- I was--seriously, I was...
to be completely honest
with you,
I had not stopped
thinking about you
after that night that we met...
- Aww.
- And I just, you know,
didn't know why that happened.
It was kind of a weird act
of fate or who-knows-what.
- Honestly, it was good
to see you again
because I was like, "Okay."
It just reassured me that--
I was like, "He's so cute."
You look great, by the way.
- You do too.
- [laughs] I was like,
"He looks great."
Um, you just have, like,
a vibe about you that--
you just make me feel,
like, secure.
- Yeah?
- Um--
- How are you on the market?
- [laughing]
- Like, I don't get this.
I'm serious, though.
Like, you are stunning.
You are
just the biggest sweetheart.
I do not understand this.
Kelley, I was so happy
that she came tonight.
There was that spark
that's, you know,
making my heart beat
a little bit faster,
and I'm just really excited.
I was looking forward
to talking to you,
and I am so happy
that you're here.
- I'm happy I'm here.
I think that there was a sign,
and, hey, I'm here.
I'm ready to take this journey
and see what the heck
that sign means.
I have no idea...
- Yeah.
- Um, but I'm ready.
- I have an amazing group
of women,
and they all
really made an impression.
I got all the hope in the world
that I just met
my wife tonight.
- Who do you guys think
is gonna get
the First Impression Rose?
- Just thinking about it kind
of makes me, like--butterflies.
- Of course we all want it,
but there's only one.
all: Yeah.
- Hello.
How you doing?
- Good.
- Hi.
- Excuse me for one second.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, there he is.
Look.
- Where is he?
- Hello, ladies.
- [screams]
- [laughs]
- Hope he feels the same way.
♪ ♪
- Hannah Ann, can I steal you
for a second?
- Yes.
- All right.
- Oop.
- I knew it.
I knew it.
- How are you feeling?
- [sighs] I'm good.
- I'm not gonna lie,
I'm really jelly.
- Aww.
- I just want to let you know
how much I appreciate,
you know, this boldness.
And you just--you touched me
with, you know, the painting
from your dad
and how close you are
with your family,
'cause that, to me,
truly means so much.
I'm just--
I'm really looking forward
to getting to know you more--
you know,
getting to know your heart--
and, uh, I definitely will say,
I think there's room
for two Hannahs...
- Oh, good, good!
- In my life.
- So--so with that being said,
Miss Hannah Ann,
will you accept this rose?
- Yes, always.
- Yes.
- I wanted you to...
- Oh, my goodness.
- Know how I felt.
- Oh, my goodness, I cannot--
- Take this,
and I'm just very excited.
- Thank you.
[sweet music]
I cannot believe I got
the First Impression Rose.
I knew when I met him there was
an instant connection,
and just looking in his eyes,
I knew, you know,
what I felt in--in my heart,
and then
actually seeing it confirmed
just means, like,
the absolute world to me.
Let's get this thing started.
- Let's go.
I'm ready.
I'm excited.
♪ ♪
[tense music]
- [clicks tongue]
Okay.
To not get that rose...
it just made me
question a lot of things.
I put myself out there
for a second.
♪ ♪
She stole him more than twice.
She had balls.
She had--she did it,
and I don't know why I didn't.
[tapping on glass]
- Sorry to break this up,
but it is time
for our first Rose Ceremony.
So...
- It is.
- Peter?
- All right, let's do this.
[suspenseful music]
Um, wow, ladies,
this has been quite the night.
So I have some...
really hard decisions,
uh, to make,
and--and I'm gonna go
try to get ready
for the ceremony.
And I guess
I'll see you guys there.
All right.
- And that's the end.
- It was a crazy night.
- It's crazy to realize, like,
of all these amazing women,
there actually are girls
that are gonna go home.
- I don't want to go home.
- I am super, super nervous.
I can only hope for the best
and hope
that he saw something--
like, a spark in me.
I'm just hoping and praying
to get a rose, at this point.
- I know. [bleep].
I haven't gotten
any more time with him
even though some girls have
got multiple time with him.
If I, like, go home tonight
and him not know who I am,
like, as a person,
that will be
literally devastating.
I'm freaking out.
- I know.
- Up next, there's tension
in the rose room.
- All these girls,
all these personalities,
it's like a ticking time bomb.
- [sighs]
Oh, God.
- And then...
it's the first date
of the season.
- Whoo!
Let's go!
- All of these girls
are gonna eat my dust!
- I'm excited
just to have time with Peter.
Like, I'm so excited.
- Who is it?
[women scream]
- Does she still like him
a little bit?
She keeps showing up.
- It's all happening tonight
on "The Bachelor"
season premiere.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- I can't believe
it's morning,
and the Rose Ceremony
is about to start
any minute now.
The tension in the room--
you can literally cut it
with a knife.
- This is the scariest thing
I've ever done.
If I went home tonight,
it would feel like
I just missed the opportunity
of a lifetime
with, like, a great guy.
So I think everyone's
just fully terrified.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
Well, ladies, um...
again, I just want to reiterate
how thankful I am
for each and every one of you,
uh, for being here tonight
and taking a chance on me.
I know it's not easy,
but what I am holding onto
is that each ceremony
will get me closer
to my forever love, and...
I'm just gonna continue
to follow my heart.
I've truly enjoyed
every conversation,
and I think my wife's in here.
I just have a lot of hope,
you know,
with this moving forward.
So if you don't
receive a rose tonight,
I wish that you may
find your love one day too.
[sweet, melancholy music]
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
- Victoria P.
- Can you guys excuse me?
♪ ♪
- Victoria,
will you accept this rose?
- Yes, I'd be honored.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
- Sure.
♪ ♪
Madison.
- [whispers] Sorry.
♪ ♪
- Madison,
will you accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
♪ ♪
- Kelley.
Kelley,
will you accept this rose?
- Of course.
♪ ♪
- Lexi.
Lexi,
will you accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- I do see the future
with Peter,
and I wanna explore
to see if he could be
really my person.
- Savannah.
- And I'll be
literally heart-shattered
if I get sent home tonight.
- Savannah,
will you accept this rose?
- Yes. Thank you.
- I would
probably bawl my eyes out.
- Lauren.
- Excuse me.
- Will you accept this rose?
- Yes, I will.
- If I do get a rose,
I'll be so freaking happy.
I'm gonna do cartwheels,
I'm gonna twerk,
and I'm going to just eat all
the cheese that I can eat.
♪ ♪
- Tammy.
Tammy,
will you accept this rose?
- Of course.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
♪ ♪
Alayah.
Alayah,
will you accept this rose?
- Of course.
- For Peter
to give me that rose,
it would mean that he feels
that there's something
really great about me.
- Jasmine.
Jasmine,
will you accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
- He's the guy I've dreamt
of marrying my whole life.
- Sydney.
♪ ♪
Sydney,
will you accept this rose?
- Yes.
- I just hope that I'm the girl
he's been dreaming of.
- Natasha.
- Excuse me.
♪ ♪
- Natasha,
will you accept this rose?
- Of course.
- I feel so strongly
that we could honestly be
the greatest love story
of all time.
- Mykenna.
♪ ♪
Mykenna,
will you accept this rose?
- Yes, of course.
♪ ♪
- Deandra.
- Excuse me.
- I meet Peter and I'm like,
"There's sparks there."
- Deandra,
will you accept this rose?
- I will.
- I do see a future
with Peter,
and I want that so badly.
- Sarah.
- [tearfully]
I didn't get time.
- Sarah,
will you accept this rose?
- Yes, yes, yes.
- So it makes me emotional.
I came here for love.
- Alexa.
- Excuse me.
- Just don't want to
lose the opportunity
to get to know him.
[sniffling]
Oh, God.
- Alexa,
will you accept this rose?
- Yes, thank you.
- But I was myself,
and I hope that was enough.
- Kelsey.
♪ ♪
Kelsey,
will you accept this rose?
- Yes, thank you.
♪ ♪
- Payton.
Payton,
will you accept this rose?
- Of course.
Thank you.
- My heart is racing
right now.
I feel just defeated.
- Kiarra.
- There's 29
other beautiful women,
and I literally feel like
he doesn't see me.
- Kiara,
will you accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
- Peter doesn't see me.
- Courtney.
♪ ♪
- I'm freaking out right now.
- Courtney,
will you accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
- If I don't
get a rose tonight,
that would be heartbreaking.
♪ ♪
- Shiann.
- Excuse me.
♪ ♪
- Shiann,
will you accept this rose?
- Hell, yes.
♪ ♪
- Ladies, Peter,
it's the final rose tonight.
When you're ready.
♪ ♪
- Victoria F.
Victoria,
will you accept this rose?
- Yes, thank you so much.
♪ ♪
- Oh, my God.
- [sighs]
Ladies, I'm sorry.
If you did not receive a rose,
take a moment,
say your good-byes.
[somber music]
[indistinct chatter]
- I'm so sad.
- Kylie, it was so nice
to meet you.
Thank you for coming.
- Yeah, thanks for having me.
Good luck.
- I wish you all the best.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
- Bye.
- Thank you so much
for coming, Maurissa.
- It was nice meeting you.
- It was a pleasure.
I wish you all the best.
- Peter's an amazing guy.
I definitely could have
seen myself
falling in love with Peter.
It sucks.
I thought
there was something there,
but I guess not.
It's--it's tough.
It's tough to go home.
- I wish you the best of luck.
- I wish you
all the best, okay?
I'm sorry.
- You know, I thought
we were meant to be together.
I didn't see this coming
at all.
♪ ♪
Maybe he just didn't like me.
I wish that I had been
more aggressive.
[sniffling]
♪ ♪
- Cheers to the most amazing
first night
I ever could have imagined.
I'm the luckiest guy
in the world.
I cannot wait
for this journey to take off.
- There's definitely gonna be
some challenges,
you know, dating Peter
in this environment.
There's gonna be jealousy.
There's gonna be some fights
and some drama.
- Cheers to being true
to ourselves
and hoping for the best.
- Peter is definitely
going to have his hands full.
All these girls,
all these personalities:
it's like a ticking,
ticking, ticking time bomb.
- Buckle up, baby.
Adventure calls.
Let's go!
[all cheer]
- Stick around.
There's more of "The Bachelor"
coming right up.
♪ ♪
It's the first date
of the season.
- These are for you, okay?
♪ ♪
- And romance takes flight.
- I think you're already
getting a sense
of how good I feel about this.
- Definitely.
- Just always hold on to that.
- But so does jealousy.
- Who is it?
[women scream]
- She just seems to just
always be here.
- The first night,
I respect it.
But why is she here?
- Do you regret
sending me home at all?
- I question it all the time.
- It's all coming up tonight
on "The Bachelor" premiere.
[engines roaring]
- Look at that.
How cool is that?
Wow.
Doesn't that just make you
feel so alive?
[engine roaring]
Whoo!
[radical rock music]
♪ ♪
Last night was a blast.
You know, feeling really good
connections right off the bat.
To me, that's huge.
♪ ♪
You know, you get one
first impression,
and I don't think it
could have started any better,
to be honest.
Uh, just really got me
excited and hopeful,
you know, for this
whole journey just to take off.
♪ ♪
I'm so excited for today.
This is my first group date
being the Bachelor.
So I better bring my A-game.
[engine sputters, turns over]
This could be, you know,
my first real date
with my wife.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, girls!
Uh, it seems like you all
got settled in just fine.
- Thank you.
- This is crazy.
Like, relationships
and connections
are about to start now.
I'm ready to start my journey
to find love with Peter.
- You know, hopefully it wasn't
lost on you last night,
but he looked at all of you,
and what did he say?
- My wife's in here.
all: My wife's in this room.
- That kind of just, like,
justified everything
that we're doing.
- I could have stepped out
of the car yesterday
to say hi to my husband
for the first time.
I'm very, very excited.
[all cheering]
- First date card
of the season is here.
- I'm stressed.
- Hopefully I'll see all of you
at the next Rose Ceremony.
- Yeah.
[all scream]
all: Bye!
- [laughs]
- The competitiveness
of last night
definitely brought out
the worst in people.
So I didn't get a lot of time
with him.
So I'm definitely hoping
that my name's
on that date card.
I wanna be able
to step my game up
knowing that
Kelley has that connection
and obviously
Hannah has that connection,
and they're only gonna
go further.
- Hannah Ann...
Kelley...
- Whoo-hoo. [laughs]
- Deandra...
- Yay.
- Tammy...
- [squeals]
[all laugh]
- Courtney...
- Yay!
- Shiann...
[indistinct chatter]
- Victoria P...
- [squeals]
- Oh!
- Jasmine, Victoria F.
- Yay!
- "Look up."
Peter.
[all gasp]
[all exclaim]
- Wait--
- What does "look up" mean?
[engine whirring]
all: Oh!
[all chattering, exclaiming]
♪ ♪
- Ladies.
[laughs]
[all cheering, chattering]
♪ ♪
- Peter buzzing around
the mansion--
I was blowing out those kisses.
Everyone was waving.
I can't wait to see my man.
- See you girls soon,
all right?
♪ ♪
[all cheering, chattering]
- First date!
- Whoo!
- Hello, ladies!
- So Peter flies in,
and he's looking
so freaking delicious.
Like, I just want to lick him
up and down.
- I'm so excited for today.
This is a really special place
for me.
Uh, this is actually
where I learned to fly
nine years ago.
My parents,
they met in the sky.
Flying just runs in my blood,
and I'm so happy
to kind of show you
why I love it so much
and, uh, put you
through the ringer.
And I invited
two very good friends
to get this show going.
[rousing militaristic music]
- Hey.
- I know.
[all chattering]
♪ ♪
- Thanks for coming.
- Nice to see you, Peter.
- Yeah, you, too.
- Hey, Peter.
Great to see you.
This is Katie Cook.
She's actually the very first
female Blue Angels pilot.
Whoo! Badass.
And we have Alisa Johnson.
She flies C-130s
for the Marines.
- Today we're going to see if
any of you have what it takes
to be Peter's copilot,
not only in the air
but also in life.
- You'd better be prepared,
because today,
we're putting you
through flight school.
all: Yeah!
- Let's do this.
- Yeah, let's go.
I have a fun day planned
for the ladies today.
It's very important for me
to find a girl
that craves adventure
as much as I do.
I need to find someone
that enjoys this,
'cause this is
what makes me so happy.
- All right, ladies.
Calculations are an important
part of being a pilot.
First lesson today
is gonna be mathematics.
- Oh, God.
- Oh, no.
- So Peter is flying you
from LA to New York.
Total distance is 3,000 miles.
She's flying
at 500 miles per hour.
How long is your trip?
- It's been a while
since I've taken any--
- Yeah, I'm like,
"I haven't been
in the eighth grade
in a long time, so"--
- Yeah, I failed math
three times in college.
So--
- Yeah.
- Okay, ready to reveal
your answers?
So it looks like
they can pass third grade.
So let's step it up
a little bit.
- This is really scary.
[laughs]
I'm so nervous.
I'm sweating.
How high, in feet,
would you and Peter have to be
to join the mile-high club?
- Oh--
- [laughs]
- 30.
- 30,000?
Is it 1,300 or 30,000?
- It's 30,000.
- Yeah, no, right.
Yeah, that's right.
That's right.
- All right,
let's reveal our answers.
Okay, 30,000 feet
is ridiculously wrong.
No.
[laughter]
- Are you going to space?
- Yeah.
Okay, back here?
Didn't even try.
That's awesome.
Okay, over here?
- All right.
- Congratulations,
that's actually right.
Next subject
is aviation terminology.
- So we're gonna give you
a aviation term
and you're gonna write
the definition
of what you think it means
on your board.
- Okay, "flying dirty."
- I think
they were a little shocked
at how dirty
aviation can sound.
- Thrust.
- Cockpit.
- Suck, squeeze, bang, blow.
- So what do you think
that'd be?
- Um, the pilot?
[both laughing]
- Peter might have a little
experience with this one:
windmilling.
- Um, having sex four times?
- [laughing]
- All right, ladies,
let's move on
to the next lesson.
[dramatic music]
- Oh, no!
- This is called a gyroscope.
Hopefully you don't throw up.
- So we have to spin
on this "orbitron"
that's like fake turbulence.
Tell my mom I love her.
You spin around one way
for a minute
and you spin around
the other way for a minute.
I, like, love thrill,
but my husband shouldn't
want me to puke for him.
[laughs]
- [squeals, laughs]
- [laughs]
- Holy [bleep].
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God...
[laughing]
- Oh, it looks painful.
Oh, [bleep].
I'm freaking out
'cause I get
motion sickness easy.
- Bend your knees.
- I'm trying.
- This is crazy.
The last time I rode on the
little teacup spinny thing,
you know, as a little girl,
I vomited.
[children screaming]
[demonic laughter]
You know, that was something
that really scared me.
It was so traumatic.
But I've never thrown up
in front of a boy before.
- Just like a rag doll.
- [laughs]
[screams]
Oh, my word.
[repeating rapidly]
- [screams]
Oh, my word.
- I don't want to do this.
I'm really, really scared.
Oh, man, I feel like [bleep].
[sinister music]
- Miss Victoria P.
trying to skimp out.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- I'm sorry,
my hand is sweating
and I'm so scared.
I'm terrified.
We have to spin
on the spinny thing,
and I'm freaking out
'cause I get
motion sickness easy.
This is gonna be a day
about conquering fears...
- Show me what you're made of.
- And, yeah.
Gonna be brave.
I'm gonna be bold,
because pain is temporary,
but Peter is
potentially forever.
Oh, my gosh.
- [laughing]
- Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my gosh.
[screams]
- Whoo!
- Oh, my gosh.
- Here we go.
- Peter--
[screams]
- Oh, my God.
- Whoo!
- Oh, my gosh,
this is terrifying.
Okay, okay,
I can't do this anymore.
I can't do it.
Seriously.
- You're stopping?
You're stopping.
That was--
I am so impressed, Victoria.
- [grunts]
I'm scared to open my eyes.
- Are you a little dizzy?
I feel so bad for Victoria P.
You could tell how nervous
she was with that gyroscope,
but she did it,
and it really showed me a lot.
[mellow music]
- [retches]
[vomit splashing]
♪ ♪
- All right,
got you some water.
Wash it down.
The fact that you just
went for that--I love that.
- This is me.
I get motion sick and then--
- [laughs]
[overlapping chatter]
- You were
such a trooper, though.
- You know, this is real life.
Sometimes we get sick
and can only hope that
someone cares enough about us
to comfort us
and to be there for us.
Peter is obviously loving
and caring.
I've never had someone
to care for me that way.
- All right, ladies, listen up.
So we went over basic math;
we reviewed
your aviation terminology,
and some of you had fun
on this gyroscope.
- So why don't you ladies
go suit up
and we'll see you
on the runway.
- "Suit up"?
- Let's get those
flight suits on, girls.
- Wait--
- Oh, what?
- Let's go, let's go.
- Day of
conquering fears, guys.
[radical rock music]
♪ ♪
- How come their flight suits
look way cuter than ours?
♪ ♪
- All right, ladies,
we're gonna face our last
and final test
in becoming Peter's copilot
with the obstacle course
in front of you.
[dramatic music]
So first, we're gonna start
with the mock turbulence.
You're gonna spin
in these chairs.
From there, you're gonna
remove the life vest
and fully inflate it.
Run up
the emergency exit slide
and down the other side.
Then you're gonna
enter the wind tunnel
and grab your boarding pass.
- Once you have
your boarding pass,
you'll see a stack of luggage.
Once you have your bag,
you're gonna
go through security,
and then you'll see a lavatory.
You'll have to change
out of your flight suit
and into the pilot's uniform.
The final two will ride
via pedal planes
and race to the finish.
- So whoever wins,
we're gonna go take
a nice sunset flight
over Los Angeles,
down the coast.
- What?
- All right, ladies,
you ready to go?
- I am about to crush this
and then go on sunset tour
with Peter.
That opportunity
is everything.
I have to win.
- Let's do it.
All of these girls
are gonna eat my dust!
Luck kiss?
- Yes.
- To victory!
- I got a need.
I got a need for Peter.
Whoo!
I'm his new Maverick.
[laughs]
- A reminder, ladies:
the winner of this
gets to be his copilot.
- Let's go.
Show me what you got!
- On your mark, get set, go!
♪ ♪
- Spin, spin, spin!
Whoo!
- Can we stop now?
I'm feeling a little vertigo.
Absolutely, I want to be
Peter's copilot,
but I'm still feeling
a little sick.
So a little bit scared.
Hopefully no throw-up.
- Let's go!
- Yes!
- Oh, it's on.
It's on.
- Wait, mine's not here.
- Let's go, Deandra!
[air hisses]
- Uh-oh!
- Whoo!
- Oh, they're going!
They're going!
- [screams]
- Whoo!
♪ ♪
Get it!
- That wind from the fan
was incredibly strong.
I was like...
[goofy exclamation]
Like, trying to do the best
that I could.
- You did it!
Come on, come on!
[punchy music]
You got it!
Three more!
♪ ♪
[hollering indistinctly]
Grab the boarding pass!
Whoo!
[laughs]
- Like, I think my eyelash
was, like, flying up
to my eyebrow.
♪ ♪
I'm, like, grabbing
onto, like, weights
and just anchoring myself
on the cement
trying to find
a stupid plane ticket.
- Find that luggage!
Come on!
Oh, we got a winner.
Go, Shiann.
There we go.
Let's go, Kelley!
Let's go!
- My bag was the one
on the bottom.
I finally find mine.
- Whoo!
Okay, come on!
Put it in there!
Guys, we got
the top three!
- Kelley was already
in the porta-potty.
Shiann's already
I change really fast.
Like, I'm like...
[gasping]
I'm literally shaking
trying to frickin'
button my stupid shirt on.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Okay, all right, I think--
I think you're good.
Let's go, let's go.
- Go.
- All right, they're off!
Final two!
Let's go!
- It's me and Kelley
at the last leg of the race
on these tricycle plane bikes.
- Let's go, girls!
- [screams]
- Come on!
Around that windmill!
Show me that stamina!
Let's go!
- Oh!
- You're cheating!
- I'm not meaning to!
- There you go!
- That's cheating!
Kelley starts going straight
right through
the freaking course.
That's so cheating!
She went through the course!
- [laughing]
- She runs through
the finish line.
It was time that
I really needed with him,
and I just lost it
because she cheated
and I played fair.
- All right, you ready?
- Yep.
- Let's go.
- I think I might
throw up again.
[melancholy music]
- I feel, like,
kind of defeated.
Kelley, like, didn't even
follow the course
and, like...
[stammers]
♪ ♪
- Whoo-hoo!
- I just really wanted
that time with him.
♪ ♪
[sniffles]
It's so annoying.
♪ ♪
[sniffles]
- I won the obstacle course,
and the reward for that
was to get a ride with Peter.
- It was beautiful.
I feel lucky.
- [laughs]
[sweet music]
- It was good to, like, just
spend some one-on-one time
with him today.
It just, like,
slowed the pace down again
and, like, just reassured me,
like, he is a catch.
Like, he's for sure a catch.
We just kind of, like,
caught up
from where we left off.
It was nice.
- This was such a cool date.
- I know.
Some of the girls
are gonna be real upset.
♪ ♪
- We're missing
a person, right?
- I think so.
She's gonna come in late, yeah.
- I wonder if they're
still together right now?
- Probably.
- Yeah.
Having that time, I mean, it's
like you're doing something--
like, 15, 20, 30, an hour.
Who knows how long
they were up there.
But, like, something that he's
really passionate about,
and that is really [bleep]
to miss out on.
- Maybe Kelley didn't realize
what she did, you know?
- But, like, I even said.
I'm like, "You're cheating."
And she still went.
- Yeah.
- Oh, you said that to her?
- Yeah, I'm like,
"You're cheating.
That's cheating."
- Right.
- Hello.
all: Hello.
You look good.
- This is super cute.
Thanks.
- Hey.
- How was your date?
- Good.
It was really good.
We went flying.
Saw, like, the mountains,
the water,
and then had to fly back.
[laughs]
- That's awesome.
- But, yeah, it was fun.
- [whispers]
Crickets.
- I--I don't want
to come off mean or anything,
'cause I don't--
I'm really happy
that you had your time
with him,
but you did cheat
throughout the obstacle course,
and I feel like that was unfair
to me and Shiann when--
- Honestly, I was just, like,
kind of going with it.
I didn't know that the rules
were gonna be, like,
extremely strict.
- It's just like,
we were all really trying
to get that time, you know?
- Um...
I don't really know
what else to do.
- Hello.
- How are you?
- How's it going?
- How you guys doing?
all: Good.
- How are you?
- [sighs]
So you guys have fun today?
- We did.
- Yeah?
I was impressed with you all.
Seriously, you killed it
out there.
But I'm excited for tonight
just to, you know,
have some one-on-one time,
get some good conversations.
And here's to tonight
and continuing the journey.
- Yes, cheers.
- All right, cheers.
- I don't think I am
the girls' favorite
right now.
A lot of them were upset
that I "cheated"
and didn't do the full course.
Plus, a couple of girls
probably don't like the fact
that I've met Peter before,
and so I feel like I have
a bunch of targets on my back.
It's good
they don't really know
we are actually at the hotel
that me and Peter met at.
I'm kind of freaked out
a little bit.
- Oh, I'm so good.
- A long day?
- [grunts]
Long day, but it was so fun.
- Yeah.
- I--yeah, I had a blast,
and you made a huge impression.
I was very--I felt horrible,
first of all.
When I was strapping in,
I see you just rushing over,
and you were
being such a trooper about it.
- That was, uh...
pretty scary,
and a little uncomfortable,
but I think that
it was worth it.
- But I can tell you were
definitely pushing yourself
through uncomfortable stuff,
and I noticed that, so--
- Yeah, 'cause, uh, I will say,
like, this whole journey
has been, you know--
definitely out
of my comfort zone.
- Mm-hmm.
- Um, today, when I was sick
and you came running
and you asked me if I was okay,
I, um...
[clicks tongue]
I'm a nurse, and I'm usually,
like, the person
that always makes sure
everyone else is okay.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I've never
had anyone, um...
be that for me.
And so--
- Hold on one second.
Stay right here.
[sweet music]
♪ ♪
I remembered something
from last night.
♪ ♪
- [laughs]
- You said you had
never received flowers
from someone before.
So I literally just
picked these right now outside.
- No, you didn't.
- These are for you, okay?
♪ ♪
- I'm really crushing
on Peter right now.
Didn't expect for it to happen
so fast.
You make me a little nervous.
- [laughs] Good.
You make me nervous too.
- Peter gives me hope
and makes me excited.
♪ ♪
I didn't know that
they made guys like that.
So...
♪ ♪
- How are you guys feeling?
- A lot of emotions.
- A lot, a lot.
- Everybody wants time
with him.
So securing that group date
or that one-on-one date,
especially, like,
just secures time with Peter.
[knocking on glass]
- [gasps]
- I'll get it.
- Wait, is that--go get it.
Go get it, go get it,
go get it, go get it.
- The stress is, like, unreal.
- Have a little
something-something.
- Let's hear it.
- Somethin'-somethin'.
- What you got?
- Does anybody else
have butterflies?
- Oh!
- Oh, my God.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- "Madison"...
- Oh, my God.
- "I want to show you
what forever looks like."
[all scream]
- Oh!
[laughs]
- Oh, my God!
- Oh!
- God!
- [laughs]
- I was not at all
expecting that.
- I really wanted that
one-on-one so badly.
I'm so much afraid of him
not choosing me
because, like, how is he
gonna feel like I'm enough
if he doesn't
give me some time
to actually show who I am?
[melancholy music]
[sniffling]
It's like,
this is what
I didn't want to do.
[sniffles]
♪ ♪
- I mean, today was a--
a hard day for me.
I got emotional, like,
after the relay and stuff
because I feel like we haven't
really,
like, had a lot of time.
- Right.
That means a lot that you cared
so much about it.
You've been wanting to go
on a sunset flight so much.
- So bad.
[conspiratorial music]
- So even though we already
had that alone time
when we flew off
in the sunset,
I would still like to get,
like, more time with Peter.
Sometimes you just
have to have more
of, like, a selfish mindset.
- Like,
I do want to, like, push myself
to, like, be able
to get that time with you.
Like, spend more time with you.
- Mm-hmm.
- I do just genuinely care.
- Yeah.
- Like, I really do.
- Do you mind if I steal him
for a minute?
- Um...
yeah, that's okay.
- All right,
I'll talk to you soon, then?
- Thanks.
- I was like,
"Okay, what the [bleep]?"
It's like, "You already
had your time for the night."
Like, I should have
just told her,
"You've had
literally all day."
Why the [bleep] did I not
say something to her?
- Do you understand
where we are?
- Uh, yeah, do you?
Wait, no, no, hold on.
Come here for one second.
- [laughing]
- We're gonna
reenact a little bit, okay?
- I know.
- This is pretty insane.
We're at the exact place
where I just randomly
ran into Kelley, um...
coming from an after-party
for my high school reunion.
She was coming back
from a wedding.
Boom, action.
Whoa, who's this right here?
- I grabbed you like this.
I was like, "Wait,
I have to tell you something."
- You're, like,
not gonna believe this.
And I was like,
"What is this?"
And then you told me.
I'm like, "No--no way.
That's insane."
- [laughing]
Oh, my God.
- Who'd have thought?
- I feel like I just sat down
and Kelley interrupted me.
And instead of me being like,
"Can I get some more time?"
- You should have.
- I know I should have,
and that's why I'm mad--
'cause I just sat down.
- I would go up there
and interrupt them instead.
- Like, I just keep
getting interrupted
by people that have had
the most time,
and I'm like literally--
- I know, that's frustrating.
It's not okay on her part.
- No, it's not okay.
- And she had
the private date with him.
Like, what else
do you need to say?
You cheated to get your time,
and now you want more time?
- So today was
a friggin' blast.
- Mm-hmm.
- I was very happy
that it was you.
I'm not naive, okay?
- Mm-hmm.
- I get that you probably have
a target on your back.
Don't let that affect you
in any way with this.
And I think you're already
getting the sense
of what I'm feeling
and how good I feel about this.
- Definitely.
- Just always hold on to that
moving forward, okay?
- I like that.
Thanks.
- Yeah?
- 'Cause I needed that.
[laughs]
- You know what else you need?
- What?
[sweet music]
To get...
- [laughing]
Oh, my God.
- On this counter.
- [giggles]
- Come here.
♪ ♪
- I mean, honestly,
a lot of today
was very, like,
Peter-and-I focused.
You know, I won and then got to
do the airplane ride with him,
and now we're in the place
that we met a month ago.
Like, there's just a lot
of signs here.
- [clicks tongue]
This rose is gonna go
to someone that kind of just--
you know,
gave it their all today.
Did what was necessary.
Um, fought for what they wanted
and just, yeah--showed me
they really wanna be here.
So with that being said,
um, Kelley,
it was pretty special
coming back where we first met.
Where that first spark, uh,
you know, kind of happened.
♪ ♪
Will you accept this rose?
- Of course.
- [laughs] Awesome.
- Thank you.
- All right.
Till next time.
- Till next time.
- All right.
- It's been a weird night.
As he, like, said to you guys,
this is actually
where I met him.
- He said "first spark."
- No, no, no, no, no.
- No, no,
he said "first spark."
Like the--
where I had my first spark.
Like, he basically was saying,
"Oh, like, I saw something
in you then."
- Oh, I didn't even catch that.
[laughs]
♪ ♪
- Nothing surprises me anymore
with this.
I, like, knew
that they, like, met before.
I didn't know that it was
at that particular place.
Like, the rest of us
didn't even have a chance.
It's just not fair.
- [laughs]
So, yeah.
- Coming up...
- You ready?
I have such a special date
planned for Madison.
[cheers and applause]
- I wasn't expecting to have
feelings, like, so soon.
Having to share you is
just gonna be really hard.
- And then...
- I don't know what to do,
like, right now.
I'm so confused.
[sighs]
I don't know.
I look at her, and I want to
just kiss her.
♪ ♪
[birds chirping]
[upbeat music]
- I'm going on a one-on-one
with Peter.
[laughs]
I honestly woke up, like,
pretty nervous,
and now I think I feel,
like, just good.
I just am ready to see him.
Like, I'm so excited.
♪ ♪
- Oh, wow.
[all scream]
- Hey.
- Oh, girl!
- Hello, beautiful.
- Damn!
- Wow, you look stunning.
- Oh, my God.
- Hello.
[overlapping chatter]
Wow.
Are you ready for today?
- I'm ready.
- This will be a fun day.
- I'm excited.
- I've got something
very special planned.
- I think today
is gonna tell a lot.
I mean, like, we're getting
the whole day,
the whole night.
[laughs, squeaks]
And it's really encouraging
to know
he felt that connection
and spark, too,
the first night.
- This is literally
my hometown.
I've driven down this road
a thousand times.
If you go all the way that way,
you go to the beach or Malibu.
- Yeah?
- And this way is towards
Westlake, where I live.
Night one.
Madison,
right from the beginning,
had such great energy.
You know,
she's a fun spirit, gorgeous.
I got a thing
for southern girls, I guess.
- Well, this is pretty,
wherever we are.
- This is a cute
little neighborhood, huh?
Today's an amazing day.
I have such a special date
planned for Madison.
You ready?
- I don't know.
- [laughs]
I'm gonna
introduce her to people
that mean the most to me.
♪ ♪
[all cheering]
[cheers and applause]
This is, um...
[laughs]
- Hi!
[upbeat music]
So you don't know this yet,
but this is obviously
my parents' house...
- Yeah?
- And they are
renewing their vows today.
- Stop!
- And, um, they don't know
you're here yet...
- Stop.
- Or any of these people.
- I'm gonna cry.
- There's a lot of family.
You know, family members
and good friends, so--
- What?
- And, uh, yeah.
So let's go say hi.
- Okay.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi!
- Hello.
all: Hi!
- I'm, like, processing
what's happening.
Like, "Oh, my gosh,
"his parents are
renewing their vows
and I'm a part of this."
I did not expect this at all.
[laughs]
- Madison, this is my aunt
from Cuba.
- Oh.
- [speaking foreign language]
- So nice to meet you.
- [speaking Spanish]
- I'm so overwhelmed
and so honored
that I get to be part
of such, like, a special,
special day.
- [whispers] Got a special one
right there.
That's Madison.
- I think love is
the most powerful
and beautiful thing
that we have,
and I'm excited to see
what that looks like
and see if, like,
that could be potential
for, like, the two of us.
- [exhales] All right.
I love you too.
You ready for this?
- I'm ready.
- Let's do it.
[playing "Bridal Chorus"]
Everyone, please rise.
♪ ♪
[chuckles]
Hello.
Well, hello, everyone.
[all laugh]
Welcome to a very special day.
Today, my parents--
Barbara and Peter Weber--
renew their vows...
in front of loving family
and friends.
Mom and Dad: surprise.
I'm an ordained minister now.
So...
[all laugh]
No, my parents--
Barbara and Peter--
are the ultimate example to me
of love--
love that you yearn for.
And you just hope
to find a love
that's as everlasting
and strong as yours.
And because of you, I know
what true love looks like.
I see it on a daily basis,
and I'm so grateful for that.
I know that
you all have written
your own vows for each other...
- Yes.
- And you'd like to share
with everyone.
- My dear sweetheart...
31 years ago,
we pledged our love
and commitment to each other.
With you, I've laughed...
I've cried...
I've cared, and I've shared,
but most importantly,
I've loved you
with all of my heart
from day one.
[sweet music]
You're my best friend
and the love of my life.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
- I've often asked myself,
"How is it possible
"that 31 years
of marriage have passed
in what seems like
the blink of an eye?"
♪ ♪
"And how did I get so lucky?"
I've loved you
for the past 33 years...
[sniffs]
And I promise to love you
for the rest of my life.
- With this understanding,
do you, Peter,
continue to take Barbara
as your beloved wife?
- I do.
- Do you, Barbara,
continue to take Peter
as your beloved husband?
- I do.
- I now pronounce
your vows renewed.
[all exclaim]
[cheers and applause]
[laughter]
♪ ♪
- We love you.
- Yay!
- Today is a very special day
for my family.
You know, being able
to share that with Madison,
I hope that shows her where
I get my inspiration from.
You look at my parents,
you feel that love.
Just the way
they look at each other.
So obvious, it's so strong.
- [cheers]
- I've been so blessed
to see that growing up,
and that's what I want.
- I feel, like, so welcomed
by everyone here,
and honestly, this was
the most incredible first date
I've ever been on in my life.
- Yeah, I'm sure it was.
- It's just so amazing,
and I just--I don't know,
I just feel like I've literally
known him my whole life,
which is just so crazy.
And I really do
see something with him,
and I think
he's really incredible.
- I mean, I have to admit,
he seems like
he's in awe of you,
and that makes me very happy,
'cause I really like you.
Give me a hug.
- Aww.
[laughs]
It's been
a really incredible day.
Like, blew every expectation
out of the water.
I'm so honored
and humbled to be here
and to be part of you guys'
special day.
This is the best date.
[both laugh]
- Welcome to our house.
- Thank you.
- I got to be a part
of what he holds
so close to his heart,
and so it just, like,
meant so much to me.
- Here we go!
- [screams]
[all cheering]
[screams]
Peter wanted me to be the one
to be here with him,
and it feels really good.
I caught the bouquet...
[laughs]
From his mom.
It's a sign.
It's a good sign.
[mellow, romantic music]
♪ ♪
- Today was so much fun.
That was as perfect, I think,
as it could have ever gone.
- Yeah.
I didn't expect to, like,
hit it off with you so well
so fast...
- Seriously, I didn't either.
- And I'm like--
I feel like I've known you
for my whole life, and it was
just so weird how I felt.
Also, like, just so comfortable
with your family
and your friends, too,
and, like, in a weird way
it felt like home.
- Yeah?
- Which is crazy to say.
But my parents have been
together for 28 years,
and just the way that
they fight for the relationship
and choose each other
every single day--
they know this is
a everlasting,
unconditional, like,
forever love.
And one thing
that my dad is so good about
is just, like, making my mom
feel like the most
important person in the room,
and I see
some of those qualities in you,
and I've always said
that I wanted to marry someone
like my dad.
I'm, like, ready
to find that person,
and I'm really serious
about that.
- Just hearing you
talk about your parents,
it's so refreshing to hear it
come from someone else--
um, how much they respect
their parents' relationship
and they admire that.
- Yeah.
- It just speaks volumes
of the kind of person you are
and your character,
and that's, you know, the type
of person I'm looking for
to spend my life with.
- I wasn't expecting to have...
[laughs]
Feelings, like, so soon.
It's scary because...
this is gonna be really hard--
like, having to share you.
- Believe me,
I know what it's like
on that side of it,
and I wish I could tell you
it's gonna get easier,
but it's probably not,
especially 'cause we're off
to such a great start
and I have such a great feeling
that feelings are just gonna
continue to develop.
- Yeah.
- But I can
see your heart already,
and I will do whatever I can
to--to protect that
and guard that for you.
And I'm just trying to live
in the present--
you know,
I'm with you right now--
and just enjoy this
and not think
about anyone else.
And...
- [laughs]
- Uh, you make it really easy
to do that.
Honestly, what we just did
earlier today
was the ultimate date for me--
better than anything--
and I could tell
that you were 100%
on the same page with me
as that.
- Yeah, and I think, like...
Yeah, like,
I do believe this works.
But I'm a very, like,
cautious person,
and I really have always
taken things really slow
in relationships.
And I've just always been
that way.
I think
you're an incredible guy,
and I trust you,
and I want you
to trust you too...
and to just, like,
trust your heart
and trust your intuition.
And if you're looking for
someone who can be your wife,
of course I want it to be me,
but I want you
to be with the person
that's the best fit for you.
Like, Mrs. Weber.
But I--I'm really hopeful,
and, um...
♪ ♪
I think you're incredible.
[chuckles]
♪ ♪
- This is a fairytale
right now, for me.
I think you're incredible too.
The fact that I can say that
so early on is--
gets me so excited for this.
This is...
[inhales deeply]
Whoo.
Today...
was such a dream
in so many ways.
It was the perfect first date
for me.
♪ ♪
Sharing the day with you
and my family--
just seeing how much you
actually appreciated it too--
for me, that means everything.
So with that being said...
[both laugh]
Madison...
- Uh-huh?
- Will you accept this rose?
- Yes.
- Yes?
- Awesome.
Come here.
♪ ♪
both: Whoo!
- [laughs]
- The night's not over.
I have one more
surprise for you.
- [laughs]
- Okay?
♪ ♪
I think you're gonna like this.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Everything else
has been great, so--
- I know, this is the best
first date ever.
- [laughs]
[band playing Tenille Arts'
"Somebody Like That"]
Oh, my God.
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
- ♪ I've seen pick-up lines ♪
♪ And dive bar strangers
slow dance ♪
♪ I've seen happy hour
two-for-ones ♪
♪ Turn to one-night stands ♪
♪ I've seen neon rebounds ♪
♪ And late-night drunk dials ♪
- Dancing with Madison
to Tenille Arts,
I just--I feel so lucky.
This is
the most amazing night,
the most beautiful girl.
- ♪ I've seen two hearts
bet it all ♪
♪ And still end up broke ♪
- I don't think the night
could get any better.
This is a fairytale.
♪ ♪
- How about
we get this party started?
Family, come on in.
♪ ♪
[cheering, laughter]
- No way!
- ♪ But I want that
all in, fallin' ♪
♪ Keep the fire burning ♪
♪ Like the first time feeling ♪
- [screams]
- ♪ If I'm gonna love ♪
♪ I'm gonna love somebody
like that ♪
♪ Kinda heart, open arms ♪
♪ Says forever
and will never ever ♪
- I feel so hopeful.
This first date
blew every expectation--
dream--
totally out of the water.
- ♪ And I want that
all-in, fallin' ♪
♪ Keep the fire burning
like the first time feeling ♪
♪ No matter what,
if I'm gonna love ♪
- I will never forget
this date.
Every part of it--it was
perfect in every single way.
- Whoo!
- ♪ Kinda heart, open arms ♪
♪ Says forever and will
never, ever take it back ♪
♪ If I'm gonna love ♪
♪ I'm gonna love
somebody like that ♪
- I'm flying high right now,
that's for sure.
This is my journey,
and everyone that I care about
was part of it today.
Just very, very grateful
that I'm able
to share that with them
and I was able
to share it with Madison.
- ♪ Love somebody like that ♪
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
[music fades]
- They probably got married.
[all laugh]
- I feel like
she's gonna get the rose.
She has him to herself.
Like, so...
- I'd love to have a date
this week.
I'd love to have that time
with Peter
and, like, be able to expand
on that relationship.
I don't want to have to wait
until the next cocktail party.
[knocking on door]
- Oh, my God.
The anticipation
is really just killer.
- I just want time with him
any way I can get it.
I will not complain.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Lauren...
- [squeals]
- Sydney...
Payton...
Natasha...
- [sighs]
God.
- Alexa...
[laughter]
Kelsey...
- Oh, thank God.
- Mykenna...
Alayah...
- [sighs]
[suspenseful music]
- Savannah.
- [sighs]
[laughs]
What a relief.
- "I hope this isn't awkward."
[all exclaim, laugh]
- "Sex-ed."
- It could be.
- That would be awkward.
- Name something more awkward
than sex-ed
with your boyfriend.
Sex-ed with your parents.
[all laugh]
- Yes.
- That would be awkward.
- Things are about to
get weird, guys.
♪ ♪
- Coming up...
- [crying]
- This is so insane.
What would you say
if I asked you to...
- [whimpers]
- Come...
- Be part of the house?
I don't--
[funky music]
♪ ♪
- [squeals]
- Hello, ladies.
[all chattering]
- So good to see you.
- Good to see you.
- I got my second group date.
I'm just excited
to hang out with the girls
and get to know them
a little bit more.
Hello.
Honestly, like,
am a little nervous
for what I have planned,
but both the first group date
and my first one-on-one,
they killed it.
So I'm hoping
we go three for three.
Well, welcome.
I am--
I am so excited for today,
and I actually have no idea
what we're doing.
[all chattering]
No, I actually asked
a very good friend of mine
that knows me very well
if they could put this date on.
Eh, a little bit nervous
'cause I have no idea
what we're doing, but...
- I'm so nervous!
- I'm excited too.
So shall we go inside and...
all: Yes!
- Find out what we're doing?
Let's go.
- It kind of makes me nervous
not to know what we're doing,
but I'm excited
to just have time with Peter.
Like...
I'm so excited.
- [laughs]
- Oh!
- [screams]
Who is this?
- I'm a little nervous,
'cause the date card said,
"I hope this isn't awkward."
So it's a million percent
going to be awkward.
- Who could that be?
[all scream]
- Hi, Peter.
- Hannah!
all: Hi, Hannah!
- Hi, girls.
- Oh, my God!
- The Beast is back, bitches.
- [laughs]
- And a windmill!
- You guys shocked?
- Oh, my God.
- We see Hannah Brown--again.
She just seems
to just always be here.
- Peter put me in charge today.
That was a terrible idea
on his part.
- Oh, no.
- I love it.
- I'm just like, "Oh, my God,
it's Hannah Brown.
But, wait, why?
Like, why are you here?"
She came by night one,
and now she's back again.
It's like,
that's a little awkward.
- We're gonna have some fun,
but before that,
I'm going to tell you the story
about this guy I once dated.
- [laughing]
- We go on a few dates,
but I still don't know
if he has what it takes
to handle the Beast.
- [laughs]
- Oh.
- And then we go
on a few more dates...
- That is so awkward.
- And we kissed.
And we didn't just kiss--
we kissed.
- This is so weird,
with my ex and then new girls.
Ay-yi-yi.
What am I doing right now?
Oh, boy.
- Our relationship...
- I'm blushing so hard
right now.
- Progresses,
and we go to Greece,
and we go to our room.
But it's not a room.
It's a windmill.
- Oh.
- Oh!
- It's romantic,
but I don't know.
I'm starting to think, like,
"Is he just a nice guy?"
Let's just say
he proved me wrong...
[laughter]
And then proved me wrong again,
and then again,
and then again in the morning.
Yeah, four [bleep] times.
[laughter]
[lighthearted music]
♪ ♪
- It's so weird.
It's so weird.
- So that is the real story
of the windmill
with old Peter and me.
[all chattering]
- Thank you, Hannah.
- Okay.
- It's bad enough
to deal with the girls
that you have to live with.
"Oh, I kissed him.
Oh, I this."
[babbles]
Blah.
all: Hi!
- But now we have to
deal with you
and your ex-girlfriend.
[laughs]
- The more confident you are
about who you are
in your sexuality,
the more confident you can be
in a relationship.
So you all are going to share
a personal story...
about sex.
- Okay.
- Oh, let's do it.
- It can be a memorable time
or just a fantasy
that you may have,
and you're gonna do this
in front of a live audience.
- [laughing]
- I knew there would be people.
- And you're...
- Hannah Brown.
- You're gonna go too.
all: Oh!
- How do I top the windmill?
I am so red right now, I bet.
- Before we all start--
Peter means a lot to me
and, uh, will always hold
a place in my heart,
and I do want him
to be able to find his person
because that's what
he deserves.
So you're gonna grab a pen
and a notepad,
and you can start writing,
and y'all can do this thing.
- Let's get going.
- Oh, my God,
I can't believe this.
I'm, like, so excited,
because I think
talking about sex is fun,
but honestly, like,
when Hannah told us a story,
I felt awkward,
'cause she was very, um...
passionate.
- It was really weird
seeing Hannah
up on stage like that.
Like, with Peter.
- Does she still like him
a little bit?
She keeps showing up.
I don't know,
Peter's assured all of us
that they've both moved on,
but, I mean, that's two times
we've seen her in a week.
- I don't know.
I know I care for him.
I know that I...
[stirring, melancholy music]
I loved him, but I--
I know it doesn't work.
Sometimes it doesn't work.
- They have a past.
So it's, like, good that
they talk about it, because--
- But don't you think
they should have handled--
like, the first night,
I totally respect it,
and it's like, "Okay, I'm
giving you your wings back."
But at the same time,
I don't know if it's necessary
for her to keep reoccurring.
- But it didn't make me
think like,
"Oh, why is she here?"
Like, you know,
I'm just kind of--
- But why is she here?
♪ ♪
- [sniffles]
[sighs, sniffles]
- Hey, birthday girl.
- I'm sorry...
[indistinct]
- Hannah.
- Hey.
- What's wrong?
- [sniffles]
- I mean,
I know this is weird, but...
- I don't know.
[inhales deeply]
I'm so sorry.
- How are you doing?
- Not--not okay.
[laughs]
- Oh, I know.
[sighs]
- Sorry.
- Come here.
- [sniffles]
- This is so weird.
- I know, I'm really sorry.
[laughs]
It's, um...
- You killed it with the story.
[laughs]
- Thanks.
- Just like I remembered.
[both laugh]
- [sniffling]
I'm really happy for you,
but it's, um...
It's just a lot.
- How is that--
how was when you came
the first night
to the mansion?
- Terrible.
- Honestly, like,
I had no idea what...
What you were gonna say or...
a little bit of me
was kind of hoping
that you weren't
just dropping something off
but that you were...
coming in and--
but I didn't need that,
and I, like, appreciated you
bringing the wings back,
and you didn't have to do that.
I gave those to you, and...
like, no matter what,
you are always gonna
mean so much to me.
Like, no matter what.
No matter how ridiculously
emotional I looked
leaving that island in Crete
and crying my eyes out.
That was insane, but--
- Um, that was...
- That was rough.
- I'm sorry.
- No, you followed
your heart, and...
- [sniffles]
I don't know.
- I can't blame you for that.
- My heart was very confused.
I don't know what I did.
I don't know.
I don't know
what the [bleep] I was doing.
I don't know...
♪ ♪
I'm...
really [bleep] up.
♪ ♪
[sniffles]
[groans]
♪ ♪
- I don't know, Peter.
I question what
I should have done.
You know, I question a lot.
[melancholy music]
♪ ♪
But, um...
[sniffles]
♪ ♪
[groans]
[sniffling]
♪ ♪
- Did you ever, um...
Like, you know
you asked Tyler out...
- Yeah.
- On the last episode.
- I know.
- You, like, ever...
did it ever cross your mind
to, like, maybe ask me instead
for that, or...?
- [inhales deeply, sighs]
- If not--
- No, no, no.
- I haven't asked you that,
and that's, like,
been on my mind...
- Um, yeah.
- For a long time.
- I...
like, there was still something
when I saw you at AFR,
I felt like.
Um...
- Why didn't...
[stammers]
I'm just being
very honest with you.
Watching that next episode
that night live
and then seeing that happen--
and then I was just like,
"Okay, well,
then, for me, that's"--
That's kind of--
like, that was it.
Like, I don't
want to be someone's,
like, a third option.
- I know.
- And so then it was just tough
'cause then I found out
that you had moved
20 minutes from where I live,
and just all this stuff
kept happening.
I don't know, I feel like
I thought that I was...
Not confused,
but now I don't know.
I don't know.
[sighs]
What the [bleep]
am I doing right now?
I don't know what I'm doing.
Uh...
Um...
Uh, yeah, yeah.
Um, what would you...
This is so insane.
What would you say
if I--I asked you to...
like, come...
And be part of the house?
- I mean...
Maybe.
Like--oh, my gosh.
I mean, there's a lot that I--
- [clears throat]
- I don't, like--um...
- Do you regret sending me home
at all in Crete?
- Yeah, Peter, I question it
all the time.
- I felt zero doubt...
Even, you know, when you said
Jed's name first.
So sure
that you were calling my name.
And then, obviously, like,
you didn't.
But that morning,
was there still--
- I mean, I told you
I--I...
had no doubts that you were...
Going to be--
it was you and Jed.
And--
- "Me and Jed"?
- Like, that you were gonna
meet my family.
Like, you were gonna
- You never told me that.
- Yes, I did.
- No, you didn't.
- Well, I don't think I wanted
to change my mind about Jed.
It was comfortable.
It was falling back
into the same thing.
But, like...
I've broke
everybody's heart in this--
and my own
through this experience.
- I mean,
I swear to you, I remember
I was at my aunt's house
watching that
live last episode,
and I was telling my parents,
"If she wants to
try this again,
I am 100% onboard."
And it just--like,
my heart just sank
when you, like,
asked Tyler out.
And I love Tyler, and it's
nothing against him, but...
[somber music]
I was just like,
"Oh, like, that hurts."
- He was, like, reaching out,
and you didn't say anything.
I didn't know where you were.
I knew you were upset
and dealing with it.
So I didn't reach out to you
and you didn't reach out to me.
I didn't know if you just
wanted get to past it,
wanted to be the Bachelor.
I mean, I thought
you wanted to be the Bachelor.
And I walked out there--
when I saw you,
I felt a lot more
than I thought I was going to.
Like, I didn't think
it would be that much spark,
because I knew there was
still something there.
- Okay, but what
does that mean?
- What do you--I don't know.
I can't--what do you mean?
Like, I don't--I don't know.
♪ ♪
What do you want--
like, what are you asking?
- [stammers]
What do you want?
Like, I'm so confused right now
'cause I'm--
I know I shouldn't
feel that way,
but I did kind of want you
to come back in.
Like, I remember I saw you
that first night
and I remember
saying, like, "Wow."
Didn't even know it was you.
I swear to God.
And then you come out,
and I then I realized
who it was, and...
♪ ♪
Like, I don't know what to do
right now.
I'm so confused,
and this is the first week
that this whole thing
has started.
And...
and I'm obviously not 100%
where I thought I was.
♪ ♪
I don't know what to do.
I can't help
how my heart feels.
I look at her and I just don't
want to stop looking at her,
and I want to just kiss her
and just...
♪ ♪
Just, like, have--
had all this work out...
♪ ♪
And it didn't,
and I know it didn't, and...
♪ ♪
I just--I feel like such a jerk
because I have such
an awesome group of girls here
expecting to meet someone
that was truly ready
to have this work
for them as well, and...
♪ ♪
[sighs]
I don't know.
[groans]
[dramatic music]
- Coming up next week
on "The Bachelor"...
- I was not gonna sit there
and stand there and be like,
"It's all right."
'Cause, no,
that's not all right.
- Hannah Brown.
- If you stay here,
you need to know
the repercussions
of what is gonna happen.
- [sobbing]
I finally get my chance
to be here
and I'm fighting for love
and, like, I'm gonna do
what I have to do.
[all sobbing]
- It just hurts.
It hurts really bad.
[sobbing]
- I don't want to
be here anymore.
He can be with Hannah,
but I'm going home.
I'm done.
- The drama continues
next week on "The Bachelor."
[pleasant music]
- All right, Ashley,
let me ask you:
what do you think of all
the ladies so far I've met?
Huh?
Am I doing good?
Little bit?
- Who's your friend?
- This is Ashley P.
- She's beautiful.
- She's gorgeous, I know.
Thinking about giving her
a First Impression Rose.
- This is, uh,
"udderly, udderly ridiculous."
- [laughs]
- You know why
the milking stool
only has three prongs to it?
- I don't.
- Because the cow
has the "udder."
- [laughs]
- Do you know why
cows have hooves?
- Why is that?
- Because they "lactose."
♪ ♪
- Oh, Chris.
I love you, Chris.
- I got dad jokes for days.
- You do.
I need to learn some of these.
- I'll take Ashley.
- Okay, all right.
- You, uh, stay here
and meet ladies.
Come on, Ashley.
- I'll try my best.
- Come on.
- "Moo-ving" on.
- You're doing great.
So stop me
if you've heard this,
but a cow walks into a bar.
[Ashley moos]